<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : CORPADS_2</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Aurubis – Metals for progressWith our metals, we create the foundation for technologies of the future. Being smart and connected doesn’t work without metals. Whether renewable energies, electric vehicles, digitalization, or urbanization, the demand for metals will continue to rise. For more than 150 years, Aurubis has produced copper and other metals that are crucial for modernization and for the ongoing development of our lives over the next decades. As a result, the company considers itself a real multimetal provider.SITE: https://aurubis.com Address Aurubis AG, Germany</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7b74e-bdb5-11ed-8cfa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:48:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Motivating Graphics</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Headquarters: 1624 Intermodal Pkwy, Haslet, Texas, 76052, United StatesPhone Number: (817) 491-4788Website: www.motivatingraphics.comRevenue: $14 MillionSince 1976, Motivating Graphics has been comprised of the most accomplished professionals in the print and packaging industry. Our focus on manufacturing premium packaging products coupled with the most technologically advanced equipment, positions MG as a world leader in the packaging industry.In an effort to best accommodate the industry trends, Motivating Graphics has created a true “One-Stop-Shop” solution with an extensive list of capabilities including: design, prototyping, transit testing, manufacturing, repair/ refurbishment and kitting and fulfillment of premium products and packaging.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d173-bdb5-11ed-bb47-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:48:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : LLF Lawyers</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>LLF Lawyers is a full service Peterborough law firm located in Peterborough with offices now in Bobcaygeon.  With 18 lawyers, supported by a team of skilled support staff, LLF Lawyers offers clients extensive experience in a diverse range of practice areas.Whether our clients are individuals or businesses, our goal is the same: to partner with them to provide personalized service, creative legal thinking, and cost effective solutions. It is the dedication and pride in client service that enables our firm to form solid and lasting relationships as trusted advisors.We are active in our community, participating in service and charitable organizations while remaining informed and knowledgeable on local issues, to bring a sensitive approach to the specific needs of our clients.SITE: www.llf.ca Address 332 Aylmer St NPeterborough, OntarioK9H 3V6, Canada(705) 742-1674</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d31a-bdb5-11ed-b6d0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:47:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Altro</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Altro have been at the forefront of innovation for 100 years. Today, working closely with architects, end customers, engineers, designers and contractors around the world, our insight and expertise help them transform everyday spaces into environments that can improve the wellbeing of everyone that uses them.And by consistently turning creative thinking into practical, real-world solutions – that maintain the highest standards of safety and durability – Altro have become synonymous with quality. As a family-founded business, we have a strong sense of what we value and a way of thinking inspired by The Bauhaus – a balance of quality, form and design-led function – that puts people’s needs at the heart of everything we do. It’s a human-centred approach to designing for the demands of 21st century life.It’s a history that means we value the bold, the brave and the new. From focusing on how the different sectors we serve need their spaces to perform, to the call for more environmentally sustainable materials, Altro are constantly challenging what is possible and seeking new ways of inspiring our customers and answering their biggest challenges.With offices across Europe, the Americas, Asia Pacific and the Middle East, we remain committed to developing solutions that stand the test of time.We combine the best in contemporary style with the functionality required to improve the way we all live and work, wherever in the world that may be.SITE: https://www.altro.com Address Works RoadLetchworth Garden CityHertfordshire, SG6 1NW</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d44d-bdb5-11ed-a166-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:47:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Mortons Media Group Ltd</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Mortons Media Group Ltd has a rich company history that stretches back into the Victorian era, and while the company has massively evolved since then, what Mortons does has stayed true to its original roots as a pioneer printers and publishers…Fast forward to today and with printing and publishing still at its core, Mortons shows no signs of slowing down. The launch of new websites, the upgrading of current systems and the introduction of new products, services and events is currently at the heart of Mortons’ activities as it embraces the exciting challenges that the new digital age has to offer.With four divisions covering publishing, events, print and mailing, Mortons Media Group Ltd continues to embody the values of quality and progress that have been ingrained into our company from the very start.Mortons offers over 20 specialist publications covering niche markets such as classic motorcycles and cars, railways and gardening, all of which are produced in-house by the many dedicated teams designing, writing and editing.Mortons also own and organise over 30 of the UK’s biggest specialist motorcycle and car events from classic bike and car shows to autojumbles and off-road motorcycles.With Mortons being named PrintWeek 2017, 2018 &amp; 2021 Regional Newspaper Printer of the Year, our coldset Web offset printing continues to provide quality printing services to more then 450 newspaper titles per month, with a print run of over 10,000,000 copies.Our final division, mailing, provides a wide range of options, from single letters to polywrapped multi-insert packs. Our mailing services aim to save customers time and money without compromising on quality.SITE: https://www.mortons.co.uk Address Media Centre Morton WayHorncastle, LincolnshireLN9 6JR, United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d545-bdb5-11ed-83c7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:47:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : ARRI</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>ARRI is a global player within the motion picture industry, employing around 1,200 staff worldwide. Named after its founders August Arnold and Robert Richter, ARRI was established in Munich, Germany, where the headquarters is still located today. Other subsidiaries are in Europe, North and South America, Asia, and Australia.The ARRI Group consists of the business units Camera Systems, Lighting, and Rental, all dedicated to connecting creativity and future technologies for moving images. ARRI is a leading designer and manufacturer of camera and lighting systems as well as system solutions for the film, broadcast, and media industries, with a worldwide distribution and service network. The portfolio includes digital cameras, lenses, camera accessories, archive technologies, lamp heads, and lighting accessories. Along with offering exclusive technologies, ARRI Rental’s first-class services and equipment provide camera, lighting, and grip packages to professional productions around the world.SITE: https://www.arri.com Address Hermann-Oberth Str. 1685640 PutzbrunnGermanyTel:+49 8945218100</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d630-bdb5-11ed-b669-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:46:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : SMLAW</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>SMT is people-focused and we try to meet the needs of our clients and staff and contribute to a better world. The attorneys and staff at SMT are dedicated to improving our community and supporting the organizations that enrich our lives and help those in need.Our law firm has grown to 24 attorneys plus support staff dedicated to providing personalized and responsive client service. From start to finish, we believe in being people-focused and making sure that each client feels listened to and valued. We want our clients to have confidence that any problem given to us will be handled with efficiency and the utmost consideration.It’s very important to us to support and give back to the community. As a firm and as individuals, we serve on boards, volunteer our time, contribute our money, and share our knowledge. We have the ability to help, and this support comes back in the form of an enhanced community. SMT attorneys and staff are involved with many different organizations that touch the community in many ways. Click on the tabs to the right to see lists of some of the organizations we are involved in. Our staff members receive one day off each year to volunteer for a nonprofit organization.SITE: https://www.smlaw.com Address 90 South E Street, Suite 200Santa Rosa, CA 95404</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d70c-bdb5-11ed-a070-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:45:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : UPONOR</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>We help our customers in residential and commercial construction, municipalities and utilities as well as in different industries to work faster and smarter, while end-users can enjoy ease and comfort.Uponor operates in three segments: Building Solutions – Europe, Building Solutions – North America and Uponor Infra.We offer a range of products and solutions for the residential market, which enable pleasant living conditions in homes. Our durable solutions help to increase efficiency in the building or renovation of single and multi-family homes.Our products for safe and hygienic drinking water delivery and energy-efficient radiant heating and cooling are also an effective solution for the commercial market. Our solutions ensure a pleasant working environment in offices, and provide possibilities to lower installation, operation and maintenance costs for different public spaces. For hotels, we offer solutions that allow their customers to be in control of their comfort by adjusting the living conditions of their own rooms, while at hospitals our solutions meet the highest standards in hygiene, without compromising comfort and energy efficiency.Our portfolio of prefabricated solutions for the commercial segment are designed to make the build and, later, maintenance processes more efficient. Our preassembled plumbing and underfloor heating manifolds and complete state-of-the art prefabricated technical walls speed up any construction or renovation project, while at the same time making operation and maintenance faster and easier.For municipalities and utilities, we offer solutions for the safe and effective distribution and management of water. Our underground infrastructure solutions can be used for the handling of stormwater, wastewater and sewage, as well as the distribution of drinking water and gas, and cable protection for electricity and telecommunications. We offer solutions for the management of stormwater, which enable surface runoffs to be directed into the stormwater network in a safe and managed way, helping to avoid flooding in urban areas. In addition to smaller wastewater and sewage systems, we offer sewer network products for municipal sewers to ensure effective sewer systems in fast-growing communities and cities.SITE: https://www.uponorgroup.com Address Äyritie 2001510 VantaaFinlandT:+358 20 129 211E:info@uponor.com</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d802-bdb5-11ed-9045-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:45:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : CEC ELECTRICAL</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>CEC ELECTRICAL, INC.CEC is one of the largest specialty contractors in Texas, serving clients in our home state and throughout the US. Our goal is to be your most trusted trade partner, delivering the highest quality of work on time and on budget without incident. Safety is at the center of our culture. We’ve implemented training programs and risk management strategies to achieve an exceptional safety EMR.We surround ourselves with outstanding people, which is what makes CEC a success story. Our vibrant staff is the backbone of CEC.Since 2009, Fortune 500 clients alive have noticed CEC as a trusted partner delivering exceptional construction solutions for private and public entities.Consistently ranked in Engineering News-Record’s top contractors lists, CEC takes pride in leading the building industry through strong leadership and a diverse portfolio.SITE: https://cecfg.com Address 1275 Valley View LaneIrving, TX 75061, US</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d8e0-bdb5-11ed-8616-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:43:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : WOODHAVEN</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Woodhaven has been dedicated to helping families make their dream homes come true. From the finest lumber to windows and doors to cabinetry and design, Woodhaven has everything a builder or homeowner needs to bring your vision to life.James T. Robinson founded Woodhaven with the goal of offering a comprehensive selection of lumber, millwork and building supplies at competitive prices, along with the friendly, knowledgeable, go-the-extra-mile service that only a family-run business can provide. Over the years, James Robinson and his sons, Alan and David, expanded Woodhaven’s offerings to include cabinetry design, flooring, and millwork and truss manufacturing to serve the growing needs of our customers. Today, Alan and David Robinson continue to lead Woodhaven with the same beliefs and integrity handed down from their father.Woodhaven’s expert staff is ready to listen to your needs and supply the best products for your project. Your home is one of the biggest investments you will ever make. It’s important to choose a building materials supplier you can rely on. We look forward to continuing to meet the needs of our customers and show you that when it comes to building materials, kitchen, flooring, and more, the name more people trust is Woodhaven.SITE: https://woodhavenlumber.com Address 200 James St, LakewoodNew Jersey, 08701United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7d9c1-bdb5-11ed-9a3e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:43:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Ennis, Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Ennis, Inc., together with its subsidiaries, engages in the production and sale of business forms and other business products in North America.The Print segment designs, manufactures, and sells business forms and printed business products including snap sets, continuous forms, laser cut sheets, tags, labels, envelopes, integrated products, jumbo rolls, and pressure sensitive products. As one of the largest providers of financial and security documents, presentation and document folders, promotional products, and advertising concept products are also produced in over 50 locations. Many facilities also provide warehousing, kitting and fulfillment. The Print segment also offers point of purchase advertising for large franchise and fast food chains. Ennis sells its products through independent dealers, including business forms distributors, stationers, printers, computer software developers, and advertising agencies in the United States.SITE: https://www.ennis.com Address 2441 Presidential PkwyMidlothian, Texas76065, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7dadd-bdb5-11ed-be98-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:42:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Sound Publishing</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Sound Publishing is the leading journalistic voice in the communities that we serve. Our 43 award-winning publications in Washington and Alaska provide vetted news and information to over 3.5-million digital viewers and 144K email subscribers each month. Each week, we distribute over 392K newspapers to our readers. Our news outlets are where the intellectually curious delve into ideas and conversations to inform their daily decisions. Whenever, and however, they choose to consume our content.SITE: https://www.soundpublishing.com Address PO Box 930Everett, WA98206-0930</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7dbbc-bdb5-11ed-a8ff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:40:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Potandon Foundation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Potandon’s senior leadership team had envisioned a day when the company could give back to the state and communities in which we live that have provided so much. Potandon Produce is surrounded by community organizations and members who make our area such a great place to live, work and raise a family. In March of 2012, those visions of giving back came to fruition with the establishment of the Potandon Foundation. Housed through the Idaho Community Foundation, the Potandon Foundation contributes to organizations throughout our area that regularly and selflessly give back to those in need. The primary focus of the Potandon Foundation is to support programs, organizations and not for profits serving children and families in crisis. Since its launch, the foundation has donated over $75,000 to local organizations who exemplify serving the community members of Idaho.SITE: https://www.potandon.com Address 1210 Pier View DriveIdaho FallsID 83402</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7dc94-bdb5-11ed-9961-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:40:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Sandals Resorts International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Since 1981, Sandals Resorts International has been leading the Caribbean all-inclusive industry by offering guests more amenities, more luxury, more innovations, and more choices than any other beach resort. Our properties are located on some of the most sought-after stretches of sand in the world, including Jamaica, the Bahamas, Saint Lucia, Grenada, Barbados, Antigua, Curacao, and Turks &amp; Caicos. From the most romantic couples-only getaways to fun-filled vacations for the whole family, our family of all-inclusive resorts share the same vision – an unwavering commitment to excellence and a promise to exceed expectations.SITE: https://www.sandals.com Address Kent Ave, Montego BaySaint James, Jamaica</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7dd67-bdb5-11ed-a0cb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Michael &amp; Son</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Since 2010, the Michael &amp; Son CARES project has been giving back to the same communities that have embraced our family-owned company from the beginning. Moreover, Michael &amp; Son has donated over $500,000 worth of complimentary work in the last 12 years. Ultimately, the goal of the Michael &amp; Son Cares Project is to restore comfort back to families when they need it most.Michael &amp; Son’s commitment to the fantastic community that has embraced us from the beginning is not only a choice but a duty. With success comes responsibility and Michael &amp; Son Cares wholeheartedly embraces the task at hand.I’ve experienced my fair share of financial struggles throughout my life, but through hard work and determination I now run one of the largest Plumbing, Electrical, and HVAC companies in the nation.Every day my technicians come across some incredible people with heartbreaking stories. When they find they have nowhere else to turn, that’s when we come in to lend a helping hand to provide comfort for a community member in need.SITE: https://michaelandson.com Address 5740 General WashingtonDr Alexandria, VA 22312</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7de37-bdb5-11ed-8e6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:39:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : ATCDT</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>ATC DrivetrainHeadquarters: 9901 W Reno Ave, Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, 73127, United StatesPhone Number: (405) 577-9901Website: www.atcdrivetrain.comRevenue: $296MATC Drivetrain is the remanufacturer of choice for an international “who’s who” of blue-chip automakers. We are the largest independent Original Equipment Supplier (OES) transmission remanufacturer in the world with an ever-growing capacity of over 1 million square feet of factory and warehouse floor space.We utilize a unique combination of progressive engineering and state of the art equipment to produce “like new” products such as transmissions and engines. Our efforts reduce both the amount of waste material and the expense of warranty fulfillment, resulting in elevated environmental standards, higher profits for our customers, and lower cost for consumers.Today, under the leadership of President and CEO, Greg Heald, the company is as active as it has ever been in the areas of growth, quality, technological advancements, and environmental considerations.In August 2021, ATC acquired the UK’s leading heavy commercial drivetrain remanufacturer, HL Smith Transmissions.With the acquisition of HL Smith, ATC is now able to provide remanufacturing services for the broadest applications in the industry, from the smallest passenger vehicles up to heavy commercial and military vehicles.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7df0b-bdb5-11ed-bdff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:39:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : PFC Brakes</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>When it boils down to it, the products we use are a reflection of who we are. You can tell a lot about a person from the products they use. Their character. Their values. Their objectives.At PFC Brakes we have used our mission to build a culture. We have built our company based on a defiant philosophy: NO COMPROMISES™ It’s a mindset, an attitude, a commitment.Set Standards. Outperform. Outlast. Surpass. Pursue Challenges. Exceed Expectations. Break Records. PFC Brakes isn’t just a product, it’s a mentality.Our passion is in our product. We strive to deliver innovative products to the market that outperform the competitors’ and all preceding products. At PFC Brakes we do not strive to meet industry standards, but to surpass them. We strive to continually drive the industry through improvement and innovation.We have built the company with people who believe in, relate to, and adopt this philosophy. A philosophy that we believe our customers share. And we respect our customers, because they don’t just adopt our company philosophy, they live it. We are all too familiar with their character, their values, their objectives, because they are ones without compromise.SITE: https://pfcbrakes.com Address 83 Carbon Metallic HighwayClover, SC 29710United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7dfdc-bdb5-11ed-8fbc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:38:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Bayou Title</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Bayou Title, Inc. was founded in 1999, by Brent and Kathleen (Kathy) Laliberte. Since then, Bayou Title has grown into the largest title insurance company in the state of Louisiana. With 20 locations statewide, we have many experienced attorneys, notaries and other professionals to service all of your real estate and legal needs. In addition, several of Bayou Title’s employees hold a Mississippi title agent license, allowing us to handle your Mississippi property closing needs. Bayou Title, Inc. has handled in excess of 70,000 real estate closings, as well as examining over 90,000 titles.Bayou Title staff also perform hundreds of hours of CE instruction to real estate agents and brokers each year. Bayou Title is an approved continuing education vendor, recognized by the Louisiana Real Estate Commission (LREC) - LIC#9065. Bayou Title also teaches a wide variety of first time homebuyer seminars for various non-profit organizations around the Greater New Orleans Metropolitan area.SITE: https://www.bayoutitle.com Address 1700 Belle Chasse Hwy.Ste. A200Gretna, LA 70056</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e0bf-bdb5-11ed-80fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:38:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Echelon Fitness</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Echelon Fitness has been revolutionizing at-home connected fitness since debuting its first Connect Bike in 2017. What began as a mission to make healthy living attainable and accessible to all evolved into a line of innovative fitness solutions—as well as a thriving community. Ranging from sophisticated indoor cycling bikes, to touch-screen fitness mirrors and more, every product boasts thoughtful design and state-of-the-art technology, enabling people to exercise how they want, when they want and with who they want. By leveraging The Echelon Fit App and United Membership, members gain access to a variety of live and on-demand classes led by down-to-earth fitness instructors. Members can also use the app to track their performance against Echelon’s live leaderboard and overall progress, all while enjoying some healthy competition.SITE: https://www.echelonfit.com Address 605 Chestnut St Ste 700Chattanooga, Tennessee37450, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e1a6-bdb5-11ed-b1b8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:37:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : The Norfolk Capital Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>The Norfolk Capital Group was founded over 30 years ago, having previously been known as Central Trust, Norfolk Capital is the vehicle through which Andrew and Sharon Turner invest in a number of companies operating in the financial services sector, providing solutions to consumers and SMEs.Companies in the portfolio have been providing a broad range of loans and other financial products to their clients since 1988.The investments of Norfolk Capital are managed through a small team based in Norwich. That team also provides specialist support services to members of the Norfolk Capital Group on an on-going or ad hoc basis. Such services include the securing of wholesale funding.Investment opportunities are judged against a number of criteria designed to ensure that Norfolk Capital’s investments meet its risk appetite and result in a portfolio providing a spread of risk in areas of business in respect of which the management team has relevant knowledge and experience.SITE: https://www.norfolkcapital.co.uk Address Norfolk Capital Group25-27 Surrey StreetNorwich, NR1 3NXTel: 01603 896 896</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e27d-bdb5-11ed-8aad-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:37:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Mettis Aerospace</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>At Mettis Aerospace, we design, manufacture and assemble precision forged and machined components at our fully integrated facility in the heart of the UK.Our vision is not only to be the best at what we do but to continually set new standards in the industry by investing and innovating.We are the forge of the future, today.We have vertically integrated centres of competence that work together and innovate to deliver excellence. That’s why we could give you the edge on your current and next generation programmes.We are renowned for our quality, in particular, and work to some of the most demanding and exacting standards in the world. We have AS9100 accreditation, NADCAP approval as well as extensive customer approvals.Come on in and discover our full range of capabilities, the products and services we offer in several sectors, the demanding quality standards we meet and how to contact us so we can work with you to develop the optimum solution for you.SITE: https://www.mettisgroup.com Address Windsor RoadRedditchWorcestershireB97 6EFTel: +44 (0)1527 406 400</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e35e-bdb5-11ed-8065-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:36:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Newly Weds Foods</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>In the food processing and foodservice industries, Newly Weds Foods is recognised as the premier global purveyor of customised breaders, batters, seasonings, and functional ingredients. Whether you’re developing products for retail or foodservice success, you’ll find our integrated resources are one of a kind. At Newly Weds Foods, we understand how important it is for your brand to stand apart. That’s why we search the world for flavours and culinary techniques that inspire customised ingredient creations. See what makes us a one-of-a-kind partner.SITE: https://newlywedsfoods.co.uk Address 86-87 Manton Rd, CorbyNorthamptonshire, NN17 4JLUnited Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e44b-bdb5-11ed-9d66-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:34:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : NOVATI</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>NOVATIWe’re experts in delivering solutions that challenge, innovate and create a better way of working, which is why we’re committed to investing in innovation at every level of our operation so that we can bring fresh ideas and technological advancement to you. The ability to review data to establish best practice is a critical tool utilised by our Corporate Innovation Consultants and Sustainability Managers.Best practice often exists with a business but isn’t shared; our ability to identify and share these solutions can significantly impact overall recycling levels. Our experience and knowledge of your sector means that we can identify best practice taking place outside of your business, which gives you the ability to assess your environmental credentials against those of your peers.SITE: https://novati.co.uk Address Cafferata Way, GamstonNottinghamshire, NG24 2TNUnited KingdomTel: +44 1636640744</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e536-bdb5-11ed-98f8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:34:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : clair</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Clair Global, or simply Clair, is a professional sound reinforcement and live touring production support company. It was founded by brothers Roy and Gene Clair, who went into business in 1966 after they were asked to bring their sound system on tour with Frankie Valli and the Four Seasons. It is believed they were the first professional sound company to tour with a band. The company formally incorporated in 1970 as Clair Bros. Audio Enterprises, Inc.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e60d-bdb5-11ed-b72f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:33:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Macomb Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Welcome to The Macomb Group! We’re proud to be a leading wholesale distributor of pipe, valves and fittings for the Midwest region and beyond.Founded in 1977 and acquired by the current owners in 1991, The Macomb Group has differentiated itself from competitors by continually expanding our operations to provide unbeatable specialty services, a huge inventory, energy-efficient solutions, and exceptional customer service.We pride ourselves on being a family and friend oriented business which started long before 1991. Our CEO Bill McGivern and Executive Vice President Keith Schatko first met while playing little league together. Years later, as fate would have it, both Schatko and McGivern were working at what was then known as Macomb Pipe &amp; Supply to help pay for college tuition. Although they knew they wanted to become business owners, they also knew how important warehouse operations were to the success of a company so they learned all they could. They started by sweeping floors, packing orders, familiarizing themselves with the products and working the sales counter. When the time came, McGivern and Schatko, together with then-partner Doug Howe purchased the company.SITE: https://www.macombgroup.com Address 6600 East 15 Mile RoadSterling Heights, MI 48312Phone: (586) 274-4100Fax: (586) 274-4125</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e6ec-bdb5-11ed-8c82-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:33:29 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : KWS</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Kanawha ScalesManufacturing · West Virginia, United States · 182 EmployeesHeadquarters:111 Jacobson Dr, Poca, West Virginia, 25159, United StatesPhone Number: (304) 755-8321Website: www.kanawhascales.comRevenue: $66.3MFounded in 1954 and Headquartered in Poca, West Virginia. Kanawha Scales &amp; Systems is a provider of various sized scales for the automotive, chemical, metals, scrap, and energy industries.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e7e4-bdb5-11ed-848b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:33:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : XLTRAILERS</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>XL Specialized TrailersHeadquarters: 1086 S 3rd St, Manchester, Iowa, 52057, United StatesPhone Number: (563) 927-4900Website: www.xlspecializedtrailer.comRevenue: $68.7MXL Specialized Trailers is a leading designer and manufacturer of highly engineered and customized trailers for applications in the heavy haul trucking, construction, agriculture, wind energy, and oil &amp; gas industries. Founded in 1995 by George Wall, XL is headquartered in Manchester Iowa. The company is a leader in the heavy haul industry—and is growing quickly. XL employs hundreds of team members at its facilities in Manchester. Artisan craftspeople make up the bulk of its workforce: Welders, Machinists, Fabricators, Painters, and Final Assemblers. In line with its strategy, the company is planning for expansion, and/or acquisition, in the foreseeable future. Over 85% of XL’s trailers are sold through a dealer network with the balance being via national accounts. XL is a wholly owned division of Bull Moose Industries, a privately owned diversified industrial company owned by the Caparo Group.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e8ab-bdb5-11ed-875d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:32:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Hall Booth Smith</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Hall Booth SmithEstablished in 1989, Hall Booth Smith, P.C. (HBS) is a full-service law firm with six regional offices strategically located throughout Georgia, as well as offices in Birmingham, Alabama; Charleston, South Carolina; Asheville, Charlotte, and Raleigh, North Carolina; Jacksonville, Miami, Tallahassee, Tampa, St. Petersburg and West Palm Beach, Florida; Nashville and Memphis, Tennessee; Little Rock and Rogers, Arkansas; Missoula, Montana; Denver, Colorado; Oklahoma City, Oklahoma; Paramus, Red Bank and Saddle Brook, New Jersey; White Plains and New York, New York. Experienced across a wide range of legal disciplines, HBS attorneys pride themselves on providing knowledgeable, proactive, client-specific counsel to individuals, domestic and international corporations, state and federal agencies, and nonprofit organizations.At HBS, we possess the legal knowledge, skill and experience to meet our clients’ needs wherever they do business. HBS maintains the highest commitment to ethically and professionally serve our clients by providing the highest quality legal representation.SITE: https://hallboothsmith.com Address 191 Peachtree St NE Ste 2900Atlanta, Georgia, 30303United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7e970-bdb5-11ed-9076-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:32:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : MAKLERSOFTWARE</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Maklersoftware GmbH is an independent provider of ASP and data center solutions for the insurance and financial market. The young company had a big challenge after the “dot com bubble” from 1999-2000 with the business model SaaS / ASP (software over Internet). Address 14 Hansestrasse, Lübeck23558, GermanyTel: +494930420860SITE: https://maklersoftware.com</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7ea35-bdb5-11ed-bcb1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:31:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : fflawoffice</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Friedman &amp; FeigerLaw Firms &amp; Legal Services · Texas, United StatesHeadquarters: 5301 Spring Valley Rd Ste 200, Dallas, Texas, 75254, United StatesPhone Number:(972) 788-1400Website: www.fflawoffice.comRevenue: $6.4MFriedman &amp; Feiger is a results-oriented law firm in Dallas, Texas, representing clients in all types of litigation matters and commercial transactions.We are hardworking attorneys with an unyielding commitment to superior legal representation. We care for our clients and aggressively pursue their rights. We approach every legal matter as a part of a relationship that will continue and grow for many years. We build our relationships with our clients on quality representation and trust.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7eafc-bdb5-11ed-b712-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:31:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : KWS_2</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Kanawha ScalesManufacturing · West Virginia, United States · 182 EmployeesHeadquarters:111 Jacobson Dr, Poca, West Virginia, 25159, United StatesPhone Number: (304) 755-8321Website: www.kanawhascales.comRevenue: $66.3MFounded in 1954 and Headquartered in Poca, West Virginia. Kanawha Scales &amp; Systems is a provider of various sized scales for the automotive, chemical, metals, scrap, and energy industries.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?6de7ebc1-bdb5-11ed-bcbf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 07:30:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Wagner CAT</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>Since 1976, Wagner has been selling and renting quality Cat machines used in heavy construction, building construction, mining, waste handling, paving, municipal and governmental applications, forestry and more.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?6de7ec9c-bdb5-11ed-9814-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 02:39:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ monti has just published a now post : Regional Transportation Authority</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/monti</link><description>A government agency created by the State of Illinois to coordinate the Chicago region’s transit system https://rtachicago.org</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/monti?6de7ed83-bdb5-11ed-a0ab-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 21:00:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Law Foundation of Silicon Valley</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Law Foundation of Silicon Valley uses innovative legal advocacy as a tool for social change. We work tirelessly to ensure that every person in our thriving region is granted the same rights and legal access. Every day, our attorneys, social workers and advocates craft inventive solutions to the life-changing legal issues facing low-income people in Silicon Valley.  Our mission is to advance the rights of under-represented individuals and families in our diverse community through legal services, strategic advocacy, and educational outreach.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6de7ee8f-bdb5-11ed-8b91-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 18:47:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : GROUPAMANA.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?6de7ef6c-bdb5-11ed-a09f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 23:36:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Minneapolis Public Schools</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Minneapolis Public Schools (MPS) or Special School District Number 1 is a public school district serving students in pre-kindergarten through twelfth grade from Minneapolis, Minnesota. Minneapolis Public Schools enrolls 36,370 students in public primary and secondary schools. The district administers about one hundred public schools including forty-five elementary schools, seven middle schools, seven high schools, eight special education schools, eight alternative schools, nineteen contract alternative schools, and five charter schools. With authority granted by the state legislature, the school board makes policy, selects the superintendent, and oversees the district's budget, curriculum, personnel, and facilities. Students speak ninety different languages at home and most school communications are printed in English, Hmong, Spanish, and Somali.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?6de7f03d-bdb5-11ed-8cfc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 08:19:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Krinos Foods</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Krinos Foods LLC is one of the largest importers and manufacturers of specialty foods in North America. Krinos imports over 3,000 frozen, refrigerated and dry food products from over 25 countries. These products include cheeses, olives, olive oils, pasta and etc.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?6de7f116-bdb5-11ed-ae26-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Wilhelm</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Egmont Wilhelm GmbHWilly-Messerschmitt-Straße 1473457 EssingenDeutschland</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?6de7f1e8-bdb5-11ed-8b12-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : PROTEKTOR</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>The Protektor brand of profiles for plaster, render and drywall has been established for over 100 years. The first to introduce the manufacture of plaster bead and drywall steel profiles for partitions and ceiling constructions in Europe we have continued to develop and innovation solutions to meet the needs of system partners and the construction industry alike.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?6de7f2b6-bdb5-11ed-ace8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Circa Jewels</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Circa Jewels is the leading international buyer of pre-owned fine jewelry, diamonds and watches. If Circa Jewels fail to take responsibility for their security weakness, all of their and their clients' confidential will be published.  File Tree - https://anonfiles.com/N52cufc5z0/filetree_txt Last date - 20th March 2023 Contact ( https://tox.chat ) - AE3750EE1BE48D86104E6FB1DADC32469A31242EFC205A3EC47EF7689E3F103472A4DBFFF399 </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?6de7f3b0-bdb5-11ed-864d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 06:58:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Kventa Kft</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Our company's main field of activity has been the trade of computing devices since the beginning. Today, our offer ranges from the installation of local networks and professional computer technology devices, through PC components to computer technology accessories, resulting in a range of several thousand products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?6de7f482-bdb5-11ed-ada1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 11:33:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : The Institute of Space Technology</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>The Institute of Space Technology (also known as IST) is a public university located in Islamabad, Pakistan. IST space program aims at designing, building, launching and succesfully operating the Pico-Satellite standard CubeSat. The program is led by Communication Systems Engineering (CSE). Established in 2002 under the auspices of the Pakistan National Space Agency. IST offers a wide array of undergraduate and graduate degrees in partnership of Beihang University and University of Surrey.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?6de7f551-bdb5-11ed-9f72-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 07:35:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : HATCHBANK.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?6de7f61c-bdb5-11ed-86d7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 06 Mar 2023 11:29:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Los Altos Foods</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>We have downloaded 1TB of your data, including full dump of customers attached below. If you will keep silence we will publish whole data pack.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6de7f6e6-bdb5-11ed-9cb8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:39:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : HAW Hamburg</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Developing sustainable solutions to the societal challenges of today and tomorrow. This is the goal of the Hamburg University of Applied Sciences (HAW Hamburg), northern Germany's leading applied sciences university when it comes to reflective practice. People from more than 100 countries help make HAW Hamburg what it is, and our diversity is our particular strength.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?6de7f7b0-bdb5-11ed-8d0e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 22:38:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Lehigh Valley Health Network</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Founded in 1899, Lehigh Valley Health Network is a healthcare network based in Allentown, Pennsylvania. The healthcare network serves Pennsylvania and its flagship hospital is Lehigh Valley Hospital.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?6de7f876-bdb5-11ed-810e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 00:02:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : AddWeb Solution Pvt</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>AddWeb Solution Pvt is a leading offshore development company provides a one-stop website, mobile, cloud, and digital marketing solution. If AddWeb Solution Pvt  fail to take responsibility for their security weakness,  all of their and their clients' confidential will be published.  File Tree - https://anonfiles.com/gab0ifc8z3/filetree_txt Last date - 19th March 2023 Contact ( https://tox.chat ) - AE3750EE1BE48D86104E6FB1DADC32469A31242EFC205A3EC47EF7689E3F103472A4DBFFF399 </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?6de7f952-bdb5-11ed-bb68-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 14:43:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : P* ***** **** L****** ***</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Indonesian company that operates in agricultural industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6de7fa21-bdb5-11ed-bb9d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 07:18:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : R****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>A manufacturer of wheels and rims from Canada.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6de7fae9-bdb5-11ed-b545-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 07:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : V******* ****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>European real estate company.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?6de7fbaf-bdb5-11ed-a92b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 05 Mar 2023 07:18:06 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>