<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : azliver.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Our MissionOur mission is to provide state-of-the-art, innovative, and compassionate care to patients affected by liver diseases.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c8e781-9fda-11ed-9aff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 13:28:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Seguros Equinoccial</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Seguros Equinoccial was born in 1973 and since then it has been a leading company in the Ecuadorian market, always seeking to provide an excellent service to its clients and the most complete insurance solutions for individuals and companies.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?d8c90515-9fda-11ed-a24a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 21:26:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ylresin.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Yuen Liang Industrial &amp; Co., Ltd. is an enterprise in Taiwan, China, with the main office in Kaohsiung City. The company operates in the Automobile Dealers sector. The company was established on January 13, 1976.Archive password is Yf$NBb</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c90702-9fda-11ed-8c90-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 21:13:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Portnoff Law Associates</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Portnoff Law Associates, Ltd. was established in Paoli, Pennsylvania in 1989 by the father – daughter team of Alan Portnoff and Michelle Portnoff. Since 1997, our practice has been limited to the collection of delinquent real estate taxes and municipal utility fees for Pennsylvania municipal governments, including municipalities, school districts and authorities.  Portnoff Law Associates strives to increase each municipal client’s revenue through the enhanced collection of delinquent real estate tax and utility fee accounts, while providing payment flexibility and excellent customer service to its residents.  Currently, we collect delinquent accounts for more than 200 municipal clients in 25 Pennsylvania counties.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c9085e-9fda-11ed-814f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 17:25:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Westmont Hospitality Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Westmont Hospitality Group was founded in 1975. This company provides aspects of hotel management, and other facility services.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c90989-9fda-11ed-8cd7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 05:23:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : EGR</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>We have specialized in the sale of telecommunications and mobile communications products for over 25 years. Through cooperation with our renowned sales partners Magenta and Drei, we have advanced to become the most successful sales company in this sector in Austria.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?d8c90aa8-9fda-11ed-a50d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 02:48:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Helicar</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?d8c90bb5-9fda-11ed-872f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 23:20:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Ultrabulk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Ultranav General Business Principles are the commitment that the company has undertaken with its stakeholders about how to conduct its business at all times, based on its values and corporate culture.  All Ultranav stakeholders, be they employees, customers, suppliers, the community or the competition, are invited to raise their doubts and/or make whistleblowing reports on the activities undertaken by our organisation.  All information reported will be treated in a confidential manner. The Ultranav Ethical Committee will critically evaluate all incoming reports and address issues according to our principles.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c90cd1-9fda-11ed-8dfd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 23:17:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Bristol Community College</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Bristol Community College is a comprehensive, public community college offering more than 130 career and transfer programs of study that lead to an associate degree in science, arts, applied sciences, and certificates of accomplishment or achievement. </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?d8c90dd8-9fda-11ed-878a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 23:19:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : ********* ******** ***** ***</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Group of Osteopathic Physicians who provide surgical health care at its highest level of expertise.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?d8c90ed7-9fda-11ed-9c79-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 19:29:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : *******</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Demo data pack of a company located in Australia.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?d8c90fd6-9fda-11ed-ba00-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 19:28:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Travis County Sheriffs Officers Association</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Travis County Sheriff's Officers Association is a company that operates in the Government industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c910da-9fda-11ed-9010-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:24:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : CHARLES P VONDERHAAR CPA WAS HACKED. MORE TNAH 50GB SENSETIVE DATA LEAKED.CHARLES P VONDER</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Who is Charles P Vonderhaar Cpa  Headquarters 10001 Alliance Rd Ste 2, Cincinnati, Ohio, 45242, United States Phone Number (513) 563-0598 Fax: (513) 563-1605 Email: chuck@cpvcpa.com</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c911da-9fda-11ed-b07c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:19:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : IOC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>IOC Company, LLC is a full service heavy civil contractor. Our primary market is the highway and road industryFounded in 2005, IOC Company, L.L.C. is a heavy civil contractor with a history of top performance in various markets. We are best known for transportation infrastructure projects. We have built our reputation on our core values: integrity, honesty, and dedication to providing superior quality to our clients. IOC Company, L.L.C. has successfully completed projects ranging from small site developments to multimillion dollar road infrastructure projects. IOC Company, L.L.C. develops and perfects each project's individual critical path in order to carefully manage every aspect of the project and avoid potential conflicts. Using the latest technology in the industry has led IOC Company, L.L.C. to produce high quality projects in an efficient manner. IOC Company, L.L.C. also produces sand, gravel, flex base (caliche) and other construction materials.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c912d6-9fda-11ed-b5d0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:09:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : ServiceMaster</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>ServiceMaster is a national company that has been a leader in the cleaning industry for more than 50 years. The local franchise in Minneapolis were founded in 1993 by people in the community who wanted to provide the best possible cleaning services to their neighbors. Since then, ServiceMaster of Minneapolis has grown to employee more than 70 people, and has encouraged a culture where your satisfaction comes first.The excellent service we are committed to providing has helped us continue to be leaders in the field of cleaning and disaster restoration for residential and commercial properties.When we come into your home or business, you can rest assured your possessions will be treated with the best care and the cleaning your property receives will be of the highest quality. We can help you get the job done – no matter how big or small, we do it all!</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c913e8-9fda-11ed-a1a6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:08:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : SOLAR INDUSTRIES INDIA WAS HACKED. MORE THAN 2TB SECRET MILITARY DATA LEAKED</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>UPDATE !!! This company did not get in touch at the specified time. In 24 hours the bidding for the sale of all company data will open. Anyone interested in buying can write in TOX: 24B03A9DA9DA26336AF573D1DA2D67782C40975A64EFE2E118FE6209049E0F6E655980C89EAB57B  Who is Solar Industries India  Solar Industries India Limited is an explosives manufacturing company. The Company manufactures, supplies and exports industrial explosives and initiating systems.  Headquarters: Solar House 14 Kachimet Amravati Rd, Nagpur, Maharashtra, 440023, India  Phone Number +91 7126634555  Revenue: $504.6M  1,891 Employees   Stock Symbol: 532725  Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/symtech-solar-group  Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/solargroupnz  Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/mssl_solarWho is Solar Industries India  Solar Industries India Limited is an explosives manufacturing company. The Company manufactures, supplies and exports industrial explosives and initiating systems.  Headquarters: Solar House 14 Kachimet Amravati Rd, Nagpur, Maharashtra, 440023, India  Phone Number +91 7126634555  Revenue: $504.6M  1,891 Employees   Stock Symbol: 532725  Linkedin: http://www.linkedin.com/company/symtech-solar-group  Facebook: http://www.facebook.com/solargroupnz  Twitter: http://www.twitter.com/mssl_solar</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c914e9-9fda-11ed-a266-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 11:15:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Somacis</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Somacis was founded in 1972. This company manufactures circuit boards and other electronics as well as technology solutions</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c915e1-9fda-11ed-93fc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 07:20:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Crescent Crown Distributing</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Crescent Crown sells and delivers more than 30 million cases annually throughout its distribution territories in Arizona and Louisiana. Crescent Crown Distributing is one of the largest distributors in the United States.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c916dc-9fda-11ed-b756-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 07:19:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : ADMIRAL Sportwetten</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?d8c917d4-9fda-11ed-9324-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 02:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Navnit Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?d8c918e8-9fda-11ed-be05-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 23:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Copper Mountain</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Copper Mountain Mining Corporation is a TSX/ASX listed copper producer, developer and explorer. Copper Mountain’s flagship asset is the 75% owned Copper Mountain mine located in southern British Columbia near the town of Princeton. The Copper Mountain mine currently produces approximately 100 million pounds of copper equivalent per year with a planned expansion to increase production to approximately 140 million pounds of copper equivalent per year.  Copper Mountain trades on the Toronto Stock Exchange under the symbol “CMMC” and Australian Stock Exchange under the symbol “C6C”</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c91a3f-9fda-11ed-8158-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 19:03:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : merlinpcbgroup.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Merlin PCB Group companies have been manufacturing and supplying PCBs to a global market for over 35 years with sustained growth based on continual investment in the very best manufacturing technology, systems and value adding services. Our Merlin Gr...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c91b3d-9fda-11ed-8b56-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 13:36:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : BOMCALCADO</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>DATA PART 1: https://anonfiles.com/O7N1M7Tfy2/bomcalcado1_zip DATA PART 2: https://anonfiles.com/K7O7MaTdy7/bomcalcado2_zip PASSWORD: Q|&amp;(A&amp;\?Le($PxD=c,_cj*hLl@+|!,K# </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?d8c91c53-9fda-11ed-b4fa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 05:22:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : First International Food co Ltd</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>DATA: https://anonfiles.com/4ew5MbT6y1/fifood_zipPASSWORD: !BJYY-U_;pvuz.dlzbd~*&gt;W;YX;x$?fM </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?d8c91d4a-9fda-11ed-90dc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 02:39:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : xlntinc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>XLNT Software Solutions offers a variety of services to end-users of our Enterprise Application Software and developers.Located in Lancaster, Pennsylvania, United States.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c91e58-9fda-11ed-b0f8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 15:15:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : elsan.care</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>stolen: 821 GB.data: marketing, finance, information of all departments of one of the company's clinics, numbers, personal data of employees, contracts, reports, internal and external contracts with policyholders, subsidiaries, etc.Elsan is a m...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c91f69-9fda-11ed-8407-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 13:52:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : IFPA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Federal Institute of Pará (IFPA) is a public educational institution, with 18 campuses, which offers technical, graduation and post-graduation courses.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c92064-9fda-11ed-b032-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 20:57:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : A?????L S?????????? ????</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Austria</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?d8c9215a-9fda-11ed-bacd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 19:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : emoney Home Loans</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>With over 25 years of expertise, we're the home for all borrowers. At emoney Home Loans, we know that no ones situation is the same and that when it comes to home loans, there's no one size fits all approach.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?d8c9224f-9fda-11ed-aa8a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : CloudCall</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>CloudCall aims to become the leading global provider of cloud solutions for small to medium businesses by simplifying their work life, taking care of their IT environment, and allowing them to focus on their core businesses.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?d8c92376-9fda-11ed-92ff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 11:28:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ibb-business-team.de</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Financing offers in Berlin for start-ups, SMEs and real estateIBB Business Team GmbH is a 100% subsidiary of the IBB Group.On behalf of the State of Berlin and the Investment Bank of Berlin (IBB), it implements various grants for start-ups, SME...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c92472-9fda-11ed-9644-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 07:28:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : miguelmechanical.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Miguel Mechanical Services Limited (MMSL) has been in existence as a service provider in the Oil and Gas Industry since 1988. With over 25 years experience as an Organization, we staff well trained, experienced and certified personnel in their relati...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c9256c-9fda-11ed-a42a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 07:16:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : payroll2u.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Hi to all!Let us introduce another IT company that provide super-secure payroll services in Asia ;) Headquartered in Singapore.Payroll2U has such clients as AirAsia, Klook, Smith &amp; Nephiew, Santen, Zimmer, etc.We have downloaded most impo... </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c92660-9fda-11ed-8182-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 20:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Pillar Resource Services</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Pillar FabricatorsFabrication Facility, Module Yard &amp; Field Service Center4155-84th AvenueEdmonton, Alberta, Canada T6B 2Z3Phone: 780-440-2212Fax:   780-440-2262Shipping/Receiving Fax: 780-440-0749OrderDesk@pillar.caOther Inquiries: info@pillar.ca</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c92759-9fda-11ed-8f13-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 13:34:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : HRL Technology Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>HRL Technology Group is a leading analytical laboratory, specialist engineering and innovation services company.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?d8c92853-9fda-11ed-a00a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 13:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : N****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Manufacturer of fire protection products</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?d8c9294b-9fda-11ed-b035-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 13:33:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : A</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>jewelry store</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?d8c92a5f-9fda-11ed-ba22-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 13:33:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Cadmet</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>At Cadmet, when we look at our customers, we don’t see job titles. We see the people behind the titles. Our business is built on human connections and strong relationships. Building them. Growing them. Sustaining them. Never taking a single relationship for granted. Ever.We are pleased to say that our approach to business – and people – has paid off. 2017 marked our 30th Anniversary as one of the first Sony Medical Dealers in the nation. Today we are one of Sony Medical’s largest nationwide dealers, with a reputation for excellent service and fair prices. And we enjoy great recognition in the medical community through our decade-long participation at regional and national trade shows that support the following industry groups:AORN – Association of periOperative Registered NursesASCA – Ambulatory Surgery Center AssociationSGNA – Society of Gastroenterology Nurses and AssociatesBiomedical Engineering Societies</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c92b7b-9fda-11ed-a473-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 03:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ daixin has just published a now post : Guardian Analytics (US)</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/daixin</link><description>Guardian Analytics is now a part of NICE Actimize, a business of NICE (Nasdaq:NICE). Consistently ranked as number one in the space, NICE Actimize is the largest and broadest provider of financial crime, risk and compliance solutions for regional and global financial institutions, as well as government regulators. With Guardian Analytics, financial institutions build trust, increase competitiveness, improve their customer experience, and scale operations.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/daixin?d8c92c79-9fda-11ed-ad15-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 17:35:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : flatironssolutions.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Flatirons Solutions provides a technical content management platform that transforms complex data into actionable information, driving measurably higher productivity, asset utilization, and compliance levels. We provide solutions and expertise that o...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c92d71-9fda-11ed-8f0f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:19:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Monmouth College</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Monmouth College is a private Presbyterian liberal arts college in Monmouth, Illinois. Monmouth enrolls approximately 900 students from 21 countries who choose courses from 40 major programs, 43 minors, and 17 pre-professional programs in a core curriculum.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?d8c92e6c-9fda-11ed-9bd6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 02:48:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : NextGen</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>NextGen Healthcare provides customized solutions to fit the exact needs of ambulatory practices. Our solutions empower patients to take control of their health and enable clinicians to be more productive and engaged.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c92f67-9fda-11ed-aad8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Fresh Del Monte</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Fresh Del Monte Produce Incorporated is one of the world’s leading vertically integrated producers, distributors, and marketers of fresh and fresh-cut fruits and vegetables. Their products include prepared fruit and vegetables, juices, beverages, snacks, and desserts, and are sold in more than 90 countries around the world.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c93061-9fda-11ed-b604-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Pharmacare</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>At Pharmacare Services, we focus on solving problems, rather than working around them. Our core values of team-based leadership, solid relationships, and deep commitment to quality and service are why hospitals rely on PharmaCare Services. Our goal is to take your pharmacy beyond functional and work towards a well-managed and well-staffed</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?d8c9316d-9fda-11ed-bed3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : tvk.nl</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Ton van Kuyk (TVK) is your Volvo dealer in North Holland for new Volvos, used Volvos and maintenance.Company that operates in the Automotive industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c93265-9fda-11ed-b7a5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 21:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : duomed.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Duomed Group is a dynamic organization with a well-established reputation and is active in consultancy, sales, integration, training and technical support of medical devices and technology for hospitals and medical practices.Local expert teams...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?d8c9335b-9fda-11ed-a512-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 19:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Alhambra-Eidos</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>https://www.zoominfo.com/c/alhambra--eidos/345908828?__cf_chl_tk=RpuNsHtJ3U8_aY_cJ.nM3xGgTjQUbdlu39sPdA54pLg-1674049852-0-gaNycGzNC-U Leaked data: https://anonfiles.com/********/Alhambra_rar Password: *&amp;YG)*7vc08V()*&amp;YguygoiugO </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?d8c9344f-9fda-11ed-bee8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : K Azarosian Costello</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>At KAZAROSIAN COSTELLO,we combine experience, knowledge and a record of success that is hard to find in other firms. In addition to our vast legal experience, the attorneys in our firm are committed to leadership at state and county bar associations. Boasting current and past presidents of bar associations including the Massachusetts Bar Association, Massachusetts Academy of Trial Attorneys, the Essex County Bar Association, and the Haverhill Bar Association, the firm has developed strong relationships in the legal community with both bench and bar.Licensed to practice in Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Maine, and California, our team provides the skilled, individualized representation our clients deserve.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c9355b-9fda-11ed-82e0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Livingston</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOFPACK - Employee documents \ Finance \  Network structure</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c93652-9fda-11ed-933c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : carinya</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Carinya Christian School Tamworth commenced in May 1984, with six students in Kindergarten to Year Three. It was started by concerned Christian parents The school was founded by the Tamworth Christian Education Association, renamed to Carinya Christian Education Ltd in 2022, as an initiative of Trinity Church. The school is one of the church's ministries, in partnership with parents and other school supporters.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?d8c93854-9fda-11ed-8daa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 13:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>