<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : NextGen</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>NextGen Healthcare provides customized solutions to fit the exact needs of ambulatory practices. Our solutions empower patients to take control of their health and enable clinicians to be more productive and engaged.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?da70fa81-97da-11ed-b2a7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 02:49:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Fresh Del Monte</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Fresh Del Monte Produce Incorporated is one of the world’s leading vertically integrated producers, distributors, and marketers of fresh and fresh-cut fruits and vegetables. Their products include prepared fruit and vegetables, juices, beverages, snacks, and desserts, and are sold in more than 90 countries around the world.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?da711306-97da-11ed-b848-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 02:47:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Pharmacare</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>At Pharmacare Services, we focus on solving problems, rather than working around them. Our core values of team-based leadership, solid relationships, and deep commitment to quality and service are why hospitals rely on PharmaCare Services. Our goal is to take your pharmacy beyond functional and work towards a well-managed and well-staffed</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?da7114b6-97da-11ed-8f17-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 02:46:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : tvk.nl</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Ton van Kuyk (TVK) is your Volvo dealer in North Holland for new Volvos, used Volvos and maintenance.Company that operates in the Automotive industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da7115de-97da-11ed-852c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 21:17:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : duomed.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Duomed Group is a dynamic organization with a well-established reputation and is active in consultancy, sales, integration, training and technical support of medical devices and technology for hospitals and medical practices.Local expert teams...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da7116fb-97da-11ed-a914-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 19:24:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Alhambra-Eidos</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>https://www.zoominfo.com/c/alhambra--eidos/345908828?__cf_chl_tk=RpuNsHtJ3U8_aY_cJ.nM3xGgTjQUbdlu39sPdA54pLg-1674049852-0-gaNycGzNC-U Leaked data: https://anonfiles.com/********/Alhambra_rar Password: *&amp;YG)*7vc08V()*&amp;YguygoiugO </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?da7117ee-97da-11ed-88ec-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 15:14:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : K Azarosian Costello</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>At KAZAROSIAN COSTELLO,we combine experience, knowledge and a record of success that is hard to find in other firms. In addition to our vast legal experience, the attorneys in our firm are committed to leadership at state and county bar associations. Boasting current and past presidents of bar associations including the Massachusetts Bar Association, Massachusetts Academy of Trial Attorneys, the Essex County Bar Association, and the Haverhill Bar Association, the firm has developed strong relationships in the legal community with both bench and bar.Licensed to practice in Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Maine, and California, our team provides the skilled, individualized representation our clients deserve.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da7118d8-97da-11ed-ad81-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:25:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Livingston</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOFPACK - Employee documents \ Finance \  Network structure</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da7119b6-97da-11ed-8b15-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 23:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : carinya</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Carinya Christian School Tamworth commenced in May 1984, with six students in Kindergarten to Year Three. It was started by concerned Christian parents The school was founded by the Tamworth Christian Education Association, renamed to Carinya Christian Education Ltd in 2022, as an initiative of Trinity Church. The school is one of the church's ministries, in partnership with parents and other school supporters.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da711a96-97da-11ed-9f7f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Jan 2023 13:41:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ hive has just published a now post : R C Stevens Construction</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive</link><description>As commercial construction specialists in Orlando, we provide new construction and renovation services with an emphasis on design/build. R. C. Stevens is qualified to design and construct any type of commercial construction project in Orlando. We offer all of the necessary resources to meet each client’s specific project needs&amp;nbsp;for design and construction services related to manufacturing/industrial,&amp;nbsp;commercial,&amp;nbsp;healthcare,&amp;nbsp;financial,&amp;nbsp;religious, and&amp;nbsp;renovations.  At. R. C. Stevens, the spirit of innovation can be found in each and every Orlando commercial construction project we do.  Every team member at R.C. Stevens strives daily to uphold the founding principles of quality and integrity as having long been a company tradition since 1926.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive?da711b8a-97da-11ed-a2b1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 23:15:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : ARC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>ARC is committed to delighting its customers with document imaging and graphic production services that help visual communication professionals do what they do best.We provide world-class service to more than 90,000 customers, including some of the biggest brands in the world. Our people work side-by-side with professionals from the most renowned companies in Hollywood, prestigious and demanding retail outlets, as well as facility managers of some of the biggest school districts in the country who use visual communication to educate their students and staff on health and safety in public areas.No matter where you look, you’ll find us striving for excellence in design and construction, education, healthcare, marketing, manufacturing, technology, sports, and hospitality.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?da711c6a-97da-11ed-84fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 22:39:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Autodelta</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Auto Delta is a company that operates in the Automotive industry.The company is headquartered in Leira, Leiria District, Portugal.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da711d5b-97da-11ed-9f74-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 21:20:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Westsächsische Hochschule Zwickau</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Pure theory - not with us. Internships, laboratory work and a strong focus on application are a matter of course in our degree programmes. We offer a well-structured course of studies that prepares you optimally for your career in a manageable time. Take a look around: More than 50 courses of study in various subject areas are waiting for you!</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da711e3c-97da-11ed-a10d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 17:31:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : University of Duisburg-Essen</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>With its 12 departments and around 40,000 students, the University of Duisburg-Essen is among the 10 largest German universities. Since 2014, research income has risen by 150 percent. Natural science and engineering are ranked within the top 10 in Germany, and the humanities are within the top 20 to 30. Especially, the physics field is ranked in the top 1 in Germany.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?da711f18-97da-11ed-bdcf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:55:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : melody.com.tr</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Melody Shipping AgenciesCapt. F. Yavuz ULUGÜN, General Manager Mr. Cemil ÇAĞLARKAYA, Balcan ÇAĞLARKAYA, Bora ULUGÜN Agency Manager title, We are pleased to introduce you the "Melody Shipping Agencies", the well-known shipping agency in Türkiye, off...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da711ff3-97da-11ed-9f40-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:55:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : atcuae.ae</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Since its inception in 1965, ATCUAE has played a leading role in the development of motorsport on both the national and international level. Today, it governs approximately 140 competitive events forming the UAE motorsport calendar, and covering disc...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da7120cb-97da-11ed-8a4c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:53:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : politriz.ind.br</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Fundada em 1989 EM UBERLÂNDIA/MG, em modestas instalações com a força de um jovem empreendedor que acreditou e viu a oportunidade de mudar sua vida e ao mesmo tempo mudar a vida de outras pessoas desenvolvendo produtos eficientes, práticos e acessíve...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da7121a3-97da-11ed-9be4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 13:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Yayla Enerji Uretim Turizm ve Insaat Ticaret</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?da71227c-97da-11ed-a229-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 11:34:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ak.com.sa</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>M.A. AL ABDUL KARIM &amp; CO. is one of the leading retail companies in the Middle East offering the reputed brands from across the world with finest product &amp; customer service.The business is carried forward based on highest retail standards support...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da712366-97da-11ed-8495-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 11:23:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : fulfilmentmatters.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Fulfilment Matters Ltd specialises in ecommerce fulfilment with a team of specialists with over 30 years of experience in fulfilment and logistics.5 gb dataencryption date ‎December ‎22, ‎2022</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da712453-97da-11ed-870b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 10:39:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Arnold Clark</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?da71252b-97da-11ed-a3d9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jan 2023 02:41:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : DAYTON PROGRESS</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?da712629-97da-11ed-bcef-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 23:19:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : El Seif Development</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Data will be published in 24 hours Stay tuned </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?da712707-97da-11ed-8c99-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 19:51:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : matrixschools.edu.my</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Matrix Global Schools provides an outstanding education: inspiring, challenging lessons, rich and varied co-curricular programmes, a warm and caring community.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da7127de-97da-11ed-bfc6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 23:12:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : TIMco</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>TIMCO is a supplier of essential products that trade professionals rely on every day. Over 7,000 quality products across all essential categories.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?da7128b4-97da-11ed-aa5e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 21:37:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Holovis</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>Holovis design and install world-class experiential solutions for global themed entertainment, visitor attractions and enterprise clients.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?da71298c-97da-11ed-91d7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 21:32:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Central Texas College</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>We offer a comprehensive array of associate degrees, career and technical training, and adult continuing education in delivery formats that address virtually every need. Our tuition rate is among the lowest in the country.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?da712ac9-97da-11ed-a0de-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Hills Salvage and Recycling</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Hills started as a bodyshop with a garage forecourt over 50 years ago. Our operation has grown rapidly in recent years, initially at our site in Burscough and now at our new home in East Gillibrands, Skelmersdale, conveniently located just off the M58.We began delivering parts in 1997 and a mail order service began the following year. We are now one of the largest and most specialised services of our type in the UK. Our move to a giant 11 acre site in Skelmersdale confirms this and redifines the professionalism of salvage and recycling business in Britain today.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da712ba9-97da-11ed-ba88-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:24:43 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Samuels and Son Seafood</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Founded in 1989 and headquartered in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, Samuels and Son Seafood produces seafood based on sustainability.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da712c86-97da-11ed-a39f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 17:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : K2 Sports</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>About K2 Sports: Our mission is to create the most innovative tools for our consumers to provide the best experiences, push the sports, and strengthen the culture. K2 was born in 1962 as America’s ski company on Vashon Island in Washington State’s Puget Sound. Renamed in 2003 as K2 Sports and now based in Seattle, the company today is an international portfolio of world-renowned brands recognized as leaders in the innovation, marketing, and quality of our products and services. Driven by a passion for our sports and enthusiasts, we make alpine skis, snowboards, snowshoes, in-line skates, and Nordic ski equipment, apparel, and accessories.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?da712d5f-97da-11ed-8446-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2023 14:37:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : NYCBAR.ORG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>New York City Bar Association</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?da712e3a-97da-11ed-a965-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : fujikura-electronics.co.th</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>33.24 GB dataFujikura - Fujikura Ltd. - a global company producing electrical equipment for power and telecommunications systems, including devices for optical fiber, such as knives and mounting devices. In 1885, Zenpachi Fujikura began manufacturi...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da712f17-97da-11ed-980d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 07:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Fu Yu Corporation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Fu Yu Corporation Limited (“Fu Yu”) provides vertically-integrated services for the manufacture of precision plastic components and the fabrication of precision moulds and dies.  ​  Since its inception in 1978, Fu Yu has grown to become one of the largest manufacturers of high precision plastic parts and moulds in Asia. Today, the Group has established a strong presence in the region with manufacturing facilities located in Singapore, Malaysia and China.  ​  Leveraging on over 40 years of operating history, Fu Yu has built a broad and diversified customer base of blue chip companies in the printing and imaging, networking and communications, consumer, medical, automotive and power tool sectors.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?da712feb-97da-11ed-a3fa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 05:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Air Comm Corporation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Air Comm Corporation (ACC) was founded in 1987 to meet the needs of helicopter operators seeking solutions to problems commonly found in factory-installed environmental control systems. Today, ACC is the industry leader in the development and manufacture of state-of-the-art bleed air heaters and vapor-cycle air conditioners for turbine helicopters.      ACC products and technical support set the industry standard; leading edge design, operating efficiency and factory service optimize environmental control and minimize maintenance expense.     Proven performance worldwide     Comprehensive, user-friendly installation guides     ACC installation technicians available for training &amp; support worldwide</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?da7130d6-97da-11ed-8719-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 05:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Trans Maldivian Airways</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>Trans Maldivian Airways is your getaway to the stunning Maldives. With the world’s largest seaplane fleet, Trans Maldivian Airways takes you from Velana International Airport in Malé to your island holiday destination. Life is about the journey, and this will likely be the most scenic one in your life. Trans Maldivian Airways currently offers transfer services to more than 80 Maldives resorts, flying over 1,000,000 passengers per year to their holiday hideaways.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?da713272-97da-11ed-97f6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 02:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Chinery and Douglas</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOFPACK - working documents</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da71335d-97da-11ed-bc99-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : T A Supply</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOFPACK - W-9 / internal documents</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da713433-97da-11ed-8beb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Ruhrpumpen</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOF PACK - Passports \ Finance \ Internal documents</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?da713504-97da-11ed-b861-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nuxe.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>NUXE, a genuine French “Love Brand”, and its founder Aliza Jabès are behind the legendary skincare products which have been essential to the day-to-day life of millions of women, such as the iconic Huile Prodigieuse®.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da7135da-97da-11ed-a792-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : russellfinex.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>About UsEstablished in 1934, Russell Finex has enjoyed 85 steady years of successful growth to become an international group employing over 250 direct employees with annual sales exceeding £40 million ($54m).As a worldwide leader in fine mesh s...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da7136af-97da-11ed-a028-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lloyddowson.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>How Lloyd Dowson began in BridlingtonLloyd Dowson Chartered Accountants, Tax, and Business Advisors were founded over forty years ago in Bridlington. We now have over 60 staff with a board of 5 directors. Two of the directors are Lloyd Dowson’s hom...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da71379b-97da-11ed-9f6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : muellergartenbau.ch</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The garden is a private refuge from the hustle and bustle of everyday life. It thrives as an oasis of relaxation and as a calling card for individual style. Our task is to optimally adapt the garden to local conditions and to create scope for creativ...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da713872-97da-11ed-900f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lidestrifoodanddrink.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>OUR INNOVATION CENTERFor most consumer product R&amp;D companies – whether working on a soup, sauce, salsa, or spirit – manufacturing happens on two scales: small-batch and full-scale production. That approach is limited, since what works in a test kit...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da713944-97da-11ed-806c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : versteden.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Versteden is specialized in the fabrication of fiberglass piping systems (Polyester, Vinyl Ester or Epoxy) either with or without a thermoplastic liner (PE, PP, PVC-U, PVC-C, PVDF or ECTFE). Its broad range of products makes it easy to choose the rig...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?da713a1e-97da-11ed-a950-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : IMI Hydronic Engineering</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>IMI plc is a global engineering group that focuses on precision fluid engineering. IMI plc incorporates three divisions, each working to make its vision come to life – IMI Hydronic, Norgren and IMI Critical.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?da713af5-97da-11ed-9cf3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 08:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : Physician Partners of America</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>Founded in 2013 by a physician-turned-entrepreneur, Physician Partners of America aims to offer patients a safe, seamless healthcare experience and doctors who can totally focus on patients. Physician Partners of America offers pain management, orthopedics, minimally invasive laser spine surgery, mental health counseling. We are</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?da713bca-97da-11ed-a605-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ hive has just published a now post : G.W. Becker</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive</link><description>***** DATA IS COMING SOON ****  G.W. Becker, Inc. is a full service, single source, provider of choice for quality overhead crane products and solutions. Family owned since 1980, we have grown from a local overhead crane parts supplier to a recognized industry leader offering a full spectrum of overhead crane related products and services throughout North America.  Proud to be an Executive Member of the Crane Manufacturer’s Association of America, we design and manufacture custom overhead cranes, hoists and components to CMAA Specifications (Class “A” through “F”) or AIST Technical Report #6. We utilize our knowledgeable in-house team of mechanical, structural and electrical engineers to offer application assistance, custom design engineering and manufacturing of overhead crane products with our customers’ needs first and foremost.  Empowered with highly trained and qualified technicians, G.W. Becker, Inc. provides self-performing installations, inspections and field service repairs for all makes and models of overhead cranes; providing compliance with local regulations and ensuring a safe and productive material handling operation.  Staying true to our mission and values, we strive to understand our customers’ needs and deliver specialized expertise and long-term planning solutions for the unique challenges of purchasing and maintaining overhead crane and hoist equipment. </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive?da713cbf-97da-11ed-8a8b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : D???? P??????s</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?da713da0-97da-11ed-98b0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 20:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : A????? ????k</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?da713e92-97da-11ed-94f2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 19:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Liebra Permana</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Liebra Permana PT was founded in 1999. The company's line of business includes the manufacturing of womens and childrens underwear.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?da713f89-97da-11ed-a583-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>