<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : NYCBAR.ORG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description>New York City Bar Association</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4555c9d3-93dc-11ed-9279-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 15:17:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : fujikura-electronics.co.th</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>33.24 GB dataFujikura - Fujikura Ltd. - a global company producing electrical equipment for power and telecommunications systems, including devices for optical fiber, such as knives and mounting devices. In 1885, Zenpachi Fujikura began manufacturi...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555e1a7-93dc-11ed-92e6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 07:18:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Fu Yu Corporation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Fu Yu Corporation Limited (“Fu Yu”) provides vertically-integrated services for the manufacture of precision plastic components and the fabrication of precision moulds and dies.  ​  Since its inception in 1978, Fu Yu has grown to become one of the largest manufacturers of high precision plastic parts and moulds in Asia. Today, the Group has established a strong presence in the region with manufacturing facilities located in Singapore, Malaysia and China.  ​  Leveraging on over 40 years of operating history, Fu Yu has built a broad and diversified customer base of blue chip companies in the printing and imaging, networking and communications, consumer, medical, automotive and power tool sectors.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?4555e390-93dc-11ed-b7d4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 05:23:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Air Comm Corporation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Air Comm Corporation (ACC) was founded in 1987 to meet the needs of helicopter operators seeking solutions to problems commonly found in factory-installed environmental control systems. Today, ACC is the industry leader in the development and manufacture of state-of-the-art bleed air heaters and vapor-cycle air conditioners for turbine helicopters.      ACC products and technical support set the industry standard; leading edge design, operating efficiency and factory service optimize environmental control and minimize maintenance expense.     Proven performance worldwide     Comprehensive, user-friendly installation guides     ACC installation technicians available for training &amp; support worldwide</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?4555e4fe-93dc-11ed-9090-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 05:20:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Trans Maldivian Airways</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>Trans Maldivian Airways is your getaway to the stunning Maldives. With the world’s largest seaplane fleet, Trans Maldivian Airways takes you from Velana International Airport in Malé to your island holiday destination. Life is about the journey, and this will likely be the most scenic one in your life. Trans Maldivian Airways currently offers transfer services to more than 80 Maldives resorts, flying over 1,000,000 passengers per year to their holiday hideaways.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?4555e634-93dc-11ed-a7de-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 02:41:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Chinery and Douglas</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOFPACK - working documents</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?4555e75f-93dc-11ed-899a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:26:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : T A Supply</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOFPACK - W-9 / internal documents</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?4555e89e-93dc-11ed-ac13-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:25:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Ruhrpumpen</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>PROOF PACK - Passports \ Finance \ Internal documents</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?4555e9d5-93dc-11ed-8bcb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 15:23:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nuxe.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>NUXE, a genuine French “Love Brand”, and its founder Aliza Jabès are behind the legendary skincare products which have been essential to the day-to-day life of millions of women, such as the iconic Huile Prodigieuse®.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555eaee-93dc-11ed-b865-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:54:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : russellfinex.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>About UsEstablished in 1934, Russell Finex has enjoyed 85 steady years of successful growth to become an international group employing over 250 direct employees with annual sales exceeding £40 million ($54m).As a worldwide leader in fine mesh s...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555ebff-93dc-11ed-95a3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 12:52:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lloyddowson.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>How Lloyd Dowson began in BridlingtonLloyd Dowson Chartered Accountants, Tax, and Business Advisors were founded over forty years ago in Bridlington. We now have over 60 staff with a board of 5 directors. Two of the directors are Lloyd Dowson’s hom...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555ed0a-93dc-11ed-9ba2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:29:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : muellergartenbau.ch</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The garden is a private refuge from the hustle and bustle of everyday life. It thrives as an oasis of relaxation and as a calling card for individual style. Our task is to optimally adapt the garden to local conditions and to create scope for creativ...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555ee12-93dc-11ed-841b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:29:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lidestrifoodanddrink.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>OUR INNOVATION CENTERFor most consumer product R&amp;D companies – whether working on a soup, sauce, salsa, or spirit – manufacturing happens on two scales: small-batch and full-scale production. That approach is limited, since what works in a test kit...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555ef1d-93dc-11ed-8fe6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:28:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : versteden.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Versteden is specialized in the fabrication of fiberglass piping systems (Polyester, Vinyl Ester or Epoxy) either with or without a thermoplastic liner (PE, PP, PVC-U, PVC-C, PVDF or ECTFE). Its broad range of products makes it easy to choose the rig...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555f026-93dc-11ed-9740-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 11:19:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : IMI Hydronic Engineering</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>IMI plc is a global engineering group that focuses on precision fluid engineering. IMI plc incorporates three divisions, each working to make its vision come to life – IMI Hydronic, Norgren and IMI Critical.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?4555f12c-93dc-11ed-8d69-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 08:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : Physician Partners of America</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>Founded in 2013 by a physician-turned-entrepreneur, Physician Partners of America aims to offer patients a safe, seamless healthcare experience and doctors who can totally focus on patients. Physician Partners of America offers pain management, orthopedics, minimally invasive laser spine surgery, mental health counseling. We are</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?4555f25a-93dc-11ed-ae68-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ hive has just published a now post : G.W. Becker</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive</link><description>***** DATA IS COMING SOON ****  G.W. Becker, Inc. is a full service, single source, provider of choice for quality overhead crane products and solutions. Family owned since 1980, we have grown from a local overhead crane parts supplier to a recognized industry leader offering a full spectrum of overhead crane related products and services throughout North America.  Proud to be an Executive Member of the Crane Manufacturer’s Association of America, we design and manufacture custom overhead cranes, hoists and components to CMAA Specifications (Class “A” through “F”) or AIST Technical Report #6. We utilize our knowledgeable in-house team of mechanical, structural and electrical engineers to offer application assistance, custom design engineering and manufacturing of overhead crane products with our customers’ needs first and foremost.  Empowered with highly trained and qualified technicians, G.W. Becker, Inc. provides self-performing installations, inspections and field service repairs for all makes and models of overhead cranes; providing compliance with local regulations and ensuring a safe and productive material handling operation.  Staying true to our mission and values, we strive to understand our customers’ needs and deliver specialized expertise and long-term planning solutions for the unique challenges of purchasing and maintaining overhead crane and hoist equipment. </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive?4555f367-93dc-11ed-9d49-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : D???? P??????s</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?4555f470-93dc-11ed-9797-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 20:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : A????? ????k</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?4555f571-93dc-11ed-a66d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 19:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Liebra Permana</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Liebra Permana PT was founded in 1999. The company's line of business includes the manufacturing of womens and childrens underwear.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?4555f692-93dc-11ed-b025-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : TIME TECHNOPLAST LIMITED</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Time Technoplast engages in manufacturing and suppling of polymer packaging products. Time Technoplast was founded in 1992.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?4555f7b0-93dc-11ed-9faa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : circlevillecourt.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Welcome to The Circleville Municipal Court website. The court serves all of Pickaway County with countywide jurisdiction.We downloaded more than 500 gigabytes of different dates. Customer data. Nanny criminals. Case information. And much more. In...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555f8ef-93dc-11ed-9286-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : ADIVA CO. LTD</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?4555fa2f-93dc-11ed-a054-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:22:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : datair.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Your negotiator obviously already got the operating money to solve this situation, but since now there is a slight upward trend in BTC - apparently he wants to make a little more money on this growth. No need to play with us. You have a deadline of J...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4555fb45-93dc-11ed-b0fe-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Chestertons Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?4555fc49-93dc-11ed-ad47-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Fire Rescue Victoria</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Fire Rescue Victoria is a fire and rescue service in the state of Victoria, Australia, that provides firefighting, rescue, HAZMAT and Emergency Medical Response services in areas of metropolitan Melbourne and major regional centres throughout Victoria.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?4555fd4d-93dc-11ed-a03e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Thor Specialties, Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?4555fe51-93dc-11ed-8a6c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Shelco</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?4555ff56-93dc-11ed-9432-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 0mega has just published a now post : Aviacode</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/0mega</link><description>Medical coding, outsourced coding, auditing &amp; consulting</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/0mega?4556005b-93dc-11ed-8cce-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ karakurt has just published a now post : River City Science Academy</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/karakurt</link><description>River City Science Academy (RCSA) is a tuition-free, public charter school located in Duval County in Jacksonville, Florida. RCSA was founded in 2007 and currently serves grades K – 12 through 4 different locations. RCSA offers an emphasis on STEM education. In this release we will show you 63 GB of RCSA's data which include financials, executive and accounting information as well as a great amount of personal student and employee data.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/karakurt?45560179-93dc-11ed-bacf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : asianrecorp.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Asian Reinsurance Corporation is an intergovernmental organization established in May 1979 under the auspices of the UN-ESCAP. Membership is open to all state members or associate members of the United Nations Economic and Social Commission for A...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4556028c-93dc-11ed-8340-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:03:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Koo Wee Rup Secondary College</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Koo Wee Rup Secondary College prides itself on building guided pathways with a wholistic approach around student centred learning. KWRSC is a Year 7 to 12 inclusive college with just over 1100 students on one campus.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?455603f0-93dc-11ed-aaa6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : millennia.pro</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>ENGINEERING  CONSULTING SERVICES 22.44 GB DATA</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?45560510-93dc-11ed-bbb7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Fruttagel</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Fruttagel was founded in 1994 when the Alfonsine plant in Ravenna was established. It combines the legacies of two important players working together in the field: Ala Frutta, a cooperative founded in the early 1960s, specializing in the processing of fresh fruit</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?4556061b-93dc-11ed-9c5b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 21:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ avoslocker has just published a now post : Corporate Interiors Inc</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/avoslocker</link><description>Corporate Interiors - Steelcase office furniture - Delaware and Philadelphia Contact Us 1-800-690-9101</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/avoslocker?45560720-93dc-11ed-806b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Duty Free Philippines</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Duty Free Philippines - In the service of Philippine Tourism. As a government corporation, DFPC is tasked to operate the duty-and tax-free merchandising system in the Philippines to augment the service facilities for tourists and to generate foreign exchange and revenue for the government.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?4556082d-93dc-11ed-93cf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Swift Academies</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>The aim of the Swift Academies is to build, strengthen and expand our Trust across the North of England, by incorporating good and outstanding schools into our family of academies and acting as a sponsor for other primary and secondary academies, aiming to help them improve their standards and performance.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?4556094d-93dc-11ed-8bab-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : 100x100banco.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>100%BancoCaracas, Venezuela</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?45560a63-93dc-11ed-8ffd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : juarez.gob.mx</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Gobierno MunicipalH. Ayuntamiento de JuárezUnidad Administrativa Benito JuárezAv. Francisco Villa 950 N., CentroC.P. 32000, Juárez, Chihuahua656 737 0000</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?45560b6c-93dc-11ed-b496-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Buffco Production, Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Buffco Production, Inc. is a native East Texas exploration and production company with more than 35 years of experience in the oil and natural gas industry. Buffco strives to drill and produce oil and gas efficiently and keep its owners informed while maintaining industry standards. Buffco understands the continuously evolving practices and technologies in the oil and gas industry, and has significant expertise with combatting shifting commodities markets. Buffco can navigate current producing properties, while methodically evaluating new prospects and strategically choosing those that fit current climates. Buffco’s adaptability and expansive knowledge base of conventional and unconventional oil and gas development are the reasons why it has had scalable growth over decades past.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?45560c75-93dc-11ed-80cc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Grupo Estrategas EMM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Grupo Estrategas S.A. de C.V es una empresa 100 % mexicana comprometida con el mercado asegurador mexicano y socialmente responsable con todos nuestros clientes, proveedores y empleados.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?45560d7c-93dc-11ed-9177-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Pendulum Associates public website of data leak</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?45560e7d-93dc-11ed-b8c5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : takamiya.co</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Takamiya provides total services from development/manufacturing, sales, rental, design/construction, management/distribution of various products including temporary equipment .Takamiya Co., LtdWe create products and services with high added value...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?45560f82-93dc-11ed-95c3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 09:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Park View</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Park View is a high performing community school in Tottenham, north London where your child will aspire, achieve and succeed.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?45561080-93dc-11ed-ab4d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Bay Area Rapid Transit</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>The San Francisco Bay Area Rapid Transit District is a heavy-rail public transit system that connects the San Francisco Peninsula with communities in the East Bay and South Bay. BART operates in five counties with 131 miles of track and 50 stations, carrying approximately 405,000 trips on an average weekday.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?455611a4-93dc-11ed-97e4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : City Lit</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Whether you are looking to kick-start a new career, delve into a favourite topic, keep active or bring some balance to a busy life, City Lit offer a huge range of courses.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?455612aa-93dc-11ed-979d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : LEK / HABO</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Lek/Habo realiseert al tientallen jaren met succes innovatieve en toonaangevende energie- en installatietechnische projecten in binnen- en buitenland.Onze vestigingen in Ter Aar (voorheen Lek Installatietechniek) en in Bodegraven (voorheen Habo) hebben hun krachten gebundeld om nog beter complexe turnkey projecten te ontwerpen, produceren, installeren en onderhouden.Met Lek/Habo bouwen we samen aan een duurzame toekomst.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?455613ab-93dc-11ed-aa86-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 17:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Bevolution Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Food &amp; Beverage · Illinois, United States﻿Bevolution Group produces shelf-stable and frozen beverage products, and cocktail mixes.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?455614ab-93dc-11ed-9ecd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 11:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : PROQUINAL Spradling Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>A team of over 1,800 people who work every day with the desire to inspire the world with designs that move people, innovations that are lasting, and products that make spaces more attractive. Always with the commitment of caring for the environment and communities we're a part of. We are Spradling: Inspiration that covers the world.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?455615ac-93dc-11ed-a9b2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Sub-drill Supply</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Sub-drill was incorporated in 1992 and is a proven and trusted manufacturer and supplier of Subsea Tools and Drilling Equipment to the Global Energy Industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?455616ad-93dc-11ed-9564-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>