<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : DGM Industrie</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>DGM Industrie is a company that operates in the Mechanical or Industrial Engineering industry. It employs 21-50 people and has $1M-$5M of revenue. </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?4fca2cb8-c4d5-11ed-88e0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : AAA Energy Service</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>AAA Energy Service Co. provides services in a multitude of market sectors to a wide variety of clients, small and large. When it comes to its experience, AAA Energy Service Co. has a diverse resume. We have developed, designed, constructed, and serviced HVAC systems throughout the commercial, industrial, and institutional marketplaces. To be successful, it takes a dedicated staff of professionals that perform at a high level of customer service and have the expertise to design and build various types of systems.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?4fca4747-c4d5-11ed-859e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : r-pac.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>korea</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca48f0-c4d5-11ed-bb1f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 12:15:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : perfectplacement.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>recruitment agency</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca4a11-c4d5-11ed-8195-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:12:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : gdz.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Fully integrated shipping line software. Provides a complete platform for managing the commercial and operational aspects of ocean carriers and agents.As a result of the attack on the this company, we also attacked its customers. In addition to the...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca4b19-c4d5-11ed-80a1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 06:41:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : VORNADO</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>was founded on the premise that comfort should be constant, bucking the trends of oscillation and utilitarian design. That still holds true today with a broad range of products that enhance efficiency and keep everyone comfortable all year long. Vornado maintains its worldwide reputation for forward-thinking products and above-and-beyond customer service from its headquarters in Andover, Kansas.SITE: https://www.vornado.com Address 415 E 13th St, AndoverKansas, 67002United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?4fca4c09-c4d5-11ed-9e0f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:17:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : MARSHALLAMPS</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Marshall has been celebrated by some of the world’s greatest bands and musicians including: Jimi Hendrix, Eric Clapton, Slash, Oasis, Muse, Gorillaz and Bring Me The Horizon. We can be seen on tour with artists like Justin Timberlake, Kendrick Lamar and Lana Del Rey. However, none of this would be possible without founder and revolutionary, Jim Marshall OBE and his son Terry.Jim was born in London on 29 July 1923 and as a child he suffered with tubercular bones which meant that he spent much of his early years hospitalised to the age of 13. At his father’s suggestion he took up tap dancing to strengthen the bones in his legs and he soon discovered that he had a flair for music. Subsequently Jim took up the drums and by the late 1930’s he was playing semi-professionally, before going on to teach.After over 20 years gigging on the road on 7 July 1960, Jim opened a family run music store with his wife Violet and son Terry called ‘Jim Marshall and Son’, at 76 Uxbridge Road, Hanwell, London. Today you will find a plaque on the pavement outside to celebrate our humble beginnings.The store sold a variety of musical instruments and attracted many young emerging talents, such as Pete Townshend, Ritchie Blackmore, John Entwistle and Big Jim Sullivan, who were friends of Terry and knew the music store through Jim’s drum students, such as Keith Moon.SITE: https://marshall.com Address Denbigh Rd, Milton KeynesMilton Keynes, MK1 1DQUnited Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?4fca4d10-c4d5-11ed-a707-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:16:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Norman S. Wright Climatec</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Norman S. Wright Climatec has rapidly grown in recent years to become one of the of premier suppliers of HVAC products and services in the Southern California market. The company’s roots began in 1996 as Airelink Products focusing mainly on air distribution products. Norman S. Wright Mechanical partnered up with Airelink to form Norman S. Wright Airelink and in the process expanded the breath of product lines with a focus on engineering and applied equipment. In 2012 the company evolved to Norman S. Wright of Southern California and continued to increase its engineering and market presence while experiencing rapid growth. With the merging with Climatec Equipment in 2014, Norman S. Wright Climatec was formed, establishing uniform coverage across all of Southern California with one of the most comprehensive offerings of HVAC products in the market.SITE: https://www.nswcla.com Address 3325 East La Palma AvenueAnaheim, CaliforniaUnited States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?4fca4dfa-c4d5-11ed-9186-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : ACEA Energia</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>ACEA EnergiaWe are working to improve residents’ daily lives by offering top quality, essential services - water, energy, lighting and waste treatment. Our aim is to constantly enhance quality, via an efficient management of our infrastructures and major investments in technological innovation. We are the number one Italian operator in the sector of integrated water services. We produce and distribute electricity and illuminate the Capital’s roads and monuments. We are in the sector of the electricity production. We are one of the leading Italian operators in the sale of electricity and gas.Our plants, located across Italy, play a major role in our business. These widely differing technological and complex facilities comprise waste-to-energy, photovoltaic, hydroelectric and thermoelectric power plants. We value our people and support their growth. We communicate to our people the Group’s principles and values and each day are committed to enhancing their sense of belonging, encouraging and supporting their training and professional growth in a fully inclusive environment.SITE: www.acea.it Address *2 Piazzale Ostiense, **Rome, 00154, Italy *Tel: +39 657991</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?4fca4edb-c4d5-11ed-9a03-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:15:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Rudman Winchell</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Rudman Winchell has the resources, personnel, and legal expertise to settle your case effectively and affordably. Our 30 plus attorneys specialize in over 40 areas of law which means that there is always a legal expert available to answer your questions, saving you time and money.*Our firm is composed of attorneys that are among the most respected in the state. Newer associates are mentored daily by a team of skilled and experienced partners. Together our attorneys expertly practice in a wide variety of law giving you the confidence that we can counsel you on the complicated or the straightforward. Rudman Winchell has the specialization your matter deserves.SITE: www.rudmanwinchell.com Address 84 Harlow St Ste 4, BangorMaine, 04401, United StatesTel: (207) 947-4501</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?4fca4fcb-c4d5-11ed-87ab-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:14:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbasta has just published a now post : Kittle’s</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta</link><description>Kittle’s offers the most and newest styles, for every budget, providing more furniture choices for your Living Room, Bedroom, Dining Room and Home Office, plus the largest selection of Mattresses from all the major brands. Over 70% of the items we sell are made or assembled here in the USA, some right here in Indiana. So whether you want something as-shown from our enormous inventory, or custom design your own creation and have exactly what you want in about 30 days, Kittle’s gives you the best value and the most personal service before, during and after the sale.More than just another furniture store - our commitment to quality and service is unmatched. Kittle’s has been recognized as a Top Workplace, awarded National Furniture Retailer of the year by Furniture Today Magazine, and consistently rated above 4-Stars! You can buy online here, but we recommend seeing furniture and especially trying out a mattress before you buy- so you’re always welcome to come browse in our showrooms - and we hope to see you soon!SITE: kittles.com Address 8600 Allisonville RdIndianapolis, IN 46250Unite State</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbasta?4fca50ac-c4d5-11ed-92dd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:13:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Ecolog International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Ecolog International is a multinational company that uses technology and supply chain management to provide services for a variety of industries including energy, construction, facility management and the environment.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?4fca5187-c4d5-11ed-9667-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Mar 2023 00:03:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : National Institute of Ocean Technology</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>The National Institute of Ocean Technology (NIOT) was established in November 1993 as an autonomous society under the Ministry of Earth Sciences in India. NIOT is managed by a Governing Council and is headed by a director. The institute is based in Chennai. The major aim of starting NIOT was to develop reliable indigenous technologies to solve various engineering problems associated with harvesting of non-living and living resources in India's exclusive economic zone, which is about two-thirds of the land area of India.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?4fca5281-c4d5-11ed-ae1f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 04:56:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : regaltax.us</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Regal Tax Advisory Group has been in business for more than 14 years. We are proud to say that we have delivered satisfaction and excellence, not just in Doral, FL and Miramar, FL, but also throughout the United States. The services we provide are al...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca536f-c4d5-11ed-af0b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:19:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : waldogeneral.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Waldo General, Inc. is a management company specializing in the management of Associated Business Units; most of which operate in the financial services industry. Waldo General, Inc.'s portfolio of businesses that it manages include storefront consum...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca5468-c4d5-11ed-8bed-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:03:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : mandirisekuritas.co.id</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Mandiri Sekuritas merupakan mitra investasi tepercaya yang menyediakan solusi pasar modal komprehensif dengan beragam produk dan layanan unggulan</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca5548-c4d5-11ed-9823-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:14:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : meatel.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Established in 1977, Meatel is a leading innovative Telecommunication, ICT and security provider and Integrator for the Public and the Private Sectors, including fixed and mobile operators. We offer a suite of services and solutions from design, supp...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca563d-c4d5-11ed-b88e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 09:18:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : buehnen.de</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Wenn wir Ihr Ziel kennen, stellen wir die richtigen Fragen und liefern das optimale Ergebnis für eine sichere und optimale Klebung Ihrer Komponenten. Für uns stehen nicht unsere Produkte im Fokus, sondern das belastbar beste Ergebnis für unsere Kunde...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca5719-c4d5-11ed-af65-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : radium.com.tw</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Radium Life Technology Co., Ltd. is developing real estate projects in Taiwan. It develops and operates the T9 BOT project, which consists of a bus terminal, four residential buildings, two office towers, a shopping mall, a hotel, and a movie theater</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca580a-c4d5-11ed-8a13-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 11:28:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ktcs.com.my</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Kilang Tin Can (Sel) Sdn Bhd (雪蘭莪製罐廠有限公司), incorporated in 1976, is a metal can manufacturing company located at Jalan Haji Sirat, Klang, Selangor.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca58e4-c4d5-11ed-98e4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 17:36:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : JAYMART.CO.TH</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca59bb-c4d5-11ed-a203-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:33:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : SERVICESTREAM.COM.AU</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca5ab5-c4d5-11ed-83f7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:33:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : WORLDMARKET.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca5ba7-c4d5-11ed-95dd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:32:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : WILDFIRE-DEFENSE.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca5c79-c4d5-11ed-973a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:32:15 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : SWEEPINGCORP.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca5d57-c4d5-11ed-b0d6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:31:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : TUEBORA.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca5e23-c4d5-11ed-b29c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:31:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : RATELINX.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca5ef0-c4d5-11ed-b10e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:30:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : FERGUSON.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca5fc1-c4d5-11ed-b4fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:30:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : ACENURSING.ORG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca60a7-c4d5-11ed-b85a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:29:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : WELLBE.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6170-c4d5-11ed-927a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:29:12 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : HELLOBRIGHTLINE.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6235-c4d5-11ed-8510-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:28:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : HITACHIENERGY.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca62fd-c4d5-11ed-b46a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:28:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : SAE.ORG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca63c2-c4d5-11ed-a1b2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:27:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : AVIDXCHANGE.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca64a1-c4d5-11ed-93db-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:27:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : GALDERMA.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca656c-c4d5-11ed-8e27-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:26:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : NEWEUROPEANOFFSHORE.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca662f-c4d5-11ed-9eea-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:25:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : MEDEXHCO.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6721-c4d5-11ed-83ff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:25:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : INVESTQUEBEC.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca67e6-c4d5-11ed-81f6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:24:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : RIOTINTO.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca68af-c4d5-11ed-8dfe-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:24:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : ITXCOMPANIES.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6976-c4d5-11ed-9f0c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : HOMEWOODHEALTH.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6a3b-c4d5-11ed-b69c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:23:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : GUINNESSPARTNERSHIP.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6b02-c4d5-11ed-a96a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:22:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : ALLIEDBENEFIT.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6c3f-c4d5-11ed-b81c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:22:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : USWELLNESS.COM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?4fca6d33-c4d5-11ed-87fc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:21:41 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : ******* A********* *********** *******</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Provider of automotive port processing services catering to domestic and foreign automotive OEMs. The company provides import, export, domestic re-marshaling and rail processing, automotive rail loading and unloading, alongside vessel marine terminal services and other related services.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?4fca6e0f-c4d5-11ed-a38b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 23:20:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Etex Communications</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>The Company’s rich heritage and continued desire to bring the very best communications services and technology to subscribers is evidenced by the evolutions of the network from open wire strung along fence posts and outhouses to the digital fiber optic network in place today.Etex Telephone Cooperative boasts a service territory of 710 square miles of rural East Texas. Customers within this service area are given the opportunity to purchase local, long distance, digital TV and internet (dial-up and DSL) services at rates comparable to those found in urban areas around the state. Deployment of fiber in the loop further enhances our ability to offer other broadband services.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?4fca6efc-c4d5-11ed-b7fd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Mar 2023 02:27:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Liberty Lines</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>For over 60 years Liberty Lines has been privileged to develop and operate one of the most effective and efficient Transit systems in the country. Today Liberty operates over 300 vehicles on 60 routes and carries almost 30 million passenger over 10 million miles annually. We believe our 700 union and non-union employees are the best transit workers in America. Our employees are our greatest asset and earn excellent wages, health and pension benefits. The Liberty workforce is foundational to the local economy.﻿Since its meager beginnings in 1953 as a 4 vehicle operation, Liberty Lines has grown through merger and acquisition to become one of the largest privately owned transportation companies in New York State. Today, the company, which is headquarted in Yonkers, operates out of 2 state of the art facilities, employing approximately 610 union and 140 non-union employees and operating a fleet of 350 vehicles from 25 foot passenger vans, to 60 foot articulated and hybrid buses.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?4fca6fd8-c4d5-11ed-becc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 01:02:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ monti has just published a now post : Cambridge College</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/monti</link><description>boston.cambridgecollege.edu</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/monti?4fca70ad-c4d5-11ed-ab14-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 12:53:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ everest has just published a now post : NRG Innovations DataBase Leak</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/everest</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/everest?4fca7199-c4d5-11ed-b041-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 02:28:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : essendant.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Essendant, formerly known as United Stationers, is a national wholesale distributor of office supplies, with consolidated net sales of $5.3 billion. Essendant stocks over 160,000 items including traditional office products, office furniture, janitori...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?4fca726d-c4d5-11ed-a2aa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 21:57:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>