<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hotdesk.me</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Hotdesk.me and their customers such as Barrington James (barringtonjames.com), Sarnac Partners (sarnacpartnertners.com), Hardman &amp; Watson (hardmanandwatson.co.uk), Penspen (penspen.com), Perkins &amp; Will (perkinswill.com), etc.We can't confirm if any...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79943fb0-af38-11ed-8a6b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 02:59:04 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : innophaseinc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>InnoPhase is a fabless semiconductor company that develops innovative and efficient RF architectures using CMOS technology. Building on our previous experience with WLAN IoT products, we have now turned our attention to building energy efficient radi...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?7994599f-af38-11ed-a5a2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 02:46:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : alliedtools.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Allied International was founded in 1962 as an import distributor of hardware products. Over the years, with our unwavering commitment to innovation, quality, value and service, we have earned the reputation as the recognized market leader in our cor...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79945b5b-af38-11ed-8041-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 17:34:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cordfinancial.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Our Story – ATM ServicesNationwide Provider of Innovative Solutions: ATM Services &amp; ProductsIn 2001, CORD Financial Services was founded by The FIKES Companies. With a small staff and hard work, CORD quickly gained success in central Texas. Throu...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79945ca9-af38-11ed-9253-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 15:38:35 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : fikes.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>https://www.fikes.com/COMMERCIAL CLEANING &amp; FACILITY MAINTENANCE SERVICESThere are many moving parts to make sure a business runs successfully, and cleanliness is the most important one. When you are looking for facility maintenance services, you...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79945db4-af38-11ed-a1f2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 15:27:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : NESG</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Group of Osteopathic Physicians who provide surgical health care at its highest level of expertise.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?79945eab-af38-11ed-9b1d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 15:26:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Fibertec</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Fibertec Environmental Services is a full-service environmental analytical laboratory, specializing in subsurface investigations, industrial hygiene, and natural gas analysis.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?79945f94-af38-11ed-aa38-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 15:26:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Suburban Laboratories</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Suburban Laboratories was founded in 1936. The original lab was located in Cicero, Illinois where it remained for over 30 years. In 1970 the lab was purchased by three professional engineers; Dr. Fred Gurnham, Robert Konvalinka and Earl Rosenberg.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?7994607c-af38-11ed-bb65-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 15:26:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : newbridge.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Founded in 1963, NewBridge Services is a non-profit organization that provides mental healthcare services to individuals of all ages.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79946159-af38-11ed-8554-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:58:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Leal Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Leal Group is a diverse group of companies contributing to the economic development of Mauritius.During the last nine decades, the Leal Group has expanded into a wide range of industries including medical, consumer goods, automotive, information technology, engineering and tourism. The Leal Group is headquartered in Moka, Mauritius.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?79946238-af38-11ed-970d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:57:56 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : AMADA WELD TECH</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Based in Southern California, AMADA WELD TECH Inc. is a leading manufacturer of equipment and systems for resistance welding, laser welding, laser marking, laser cutting, laser micromachining, and hot bar bonding. Visit our Virtual Showroom!The company provides products to a wide range of markets, including the medical device, battery, electric vehicle and solar industries, as well as the global electronics, automotive and general industrial markets.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?7994633f-af38-11ed-93d5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:57:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Hengmei Optoelectronics Co.,Ltd.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Hengmei Optoelectronics Co., Ltd. was established in May 2014, located in Kunshan Development Zone, Jiangsu Province, with a registered capital of 3.25278 billion yuan. At present, four production bases in Kunshan, Fuzhou, Hefei and Danyang have been established and planned, and the total annual production capacity of polarizers is planned to be 220 million square meters. It will become the world's leading polarizer manufacturer and provide high-quality panel factories in many countries and regions around the world. , Stable polarizer supply. Among them, Hengmei Kunshan factory has a total of two polarizer production lines. Line 1 has a width of 1.5M. It was officially mass-produced in January 2017, with a monthly production capacity of 1.8 million square meters. Line 2 has a width of 2.5M and began mass production in September 2019. , with a monthly production capacity of 3.2 million square meters. The two lines have achieved an annual production capacity of 60 million square meters. Hengmei Fuzhou factory has newly added two 2.6M ultra-wide polarizer production lines. It is planned to start mass production in Q4 of 2022. After full production, the two lines will have an annual production capacity of 90 million square meters.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?79946420-af38-11ed-b6d1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:56:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Cansew</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Cansew has been part of the fabric of life since 1924. When it comes time to place your orders, you will find that our more than 80 years of experience and our position as a leading supplier of threads and trim to the needletrade industry will serve your needs exce</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?799464fa-af38-11ed-9135-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:56:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Wawasee Community School Corporation</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>The Wawasee Community School Corporation works to create an academic, social, and physical environment that facilitates growth in each student. They are headquartered in Syracuse, Indiana</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?799465ee-af38-11ed-94cf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 10:54:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : AP Emissions Technologies</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Automotive Parts · North Carolina, United States AP® Emissions Technologies is one of the leading manufacturers and suppliers of automotive, light truck, and heavy-duty exhaust and emissions products under the AP®, DuraFit®, Eastern Catalytic®, CATCO ®, ANSA®, Cherry Bomb®, DieselTech™, DuraFit™, Maremont®, XLERA and much more.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?799466cd-af38-11ed-a4b6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 07:23:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vissan.com.vn</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>VISSAN Joint Stock Company is one of the leading business corporations in Vietnam. Originally founded on November 20, 1970 and launched on May 18, 1974, VISSAN is proud to become one of the leading nationally recognized food producers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?799467c4-af38-11ed-86f3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 02:51:54 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : myerspower.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>myerspower.comlabriegroup.commielectric.comaeti.comthese four companies were in the same domain! all their networks were encryptedroot:gear$N0stra*aeti\admin:_NYt7~St]ye'root:$a53ty!myersamerica\tadmin:$a53ty!myerspower:Xiw6zvbp37gx...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?799468a5-af38-11ed-9730-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 23:23:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vitrox.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>ViTrox Corporation Berhad (MYX: 0097) is a Malaysian based electronics company located at Penang, Malaysia. Vitrox specializes in designing and developing automated vision inspection system and equipment testers for the semiconductor and electronic p...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79946984-af38-11ed-964e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:48:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ziapueblo.org</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Pueblo of Zia has operated a contemporary court since 2007. It is a court of general jurisdiction and oversees criminal and civil hearings. Currently the Court staff consists of a Chief Judge (part-time), a court clerk and a part time probation o...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79946a76-af38-11ed-93c9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:43:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : royallepage.ca</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Since 1913, Royal LePage has been helping Canadians buy and sell their homes and supporting communitiesQuebec City branch</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79946b51-af38-11ed-9d2b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 21:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Evans Consoles</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>For over four decades, Evans has been the global leader in providing innovative solutions for mission-critical operations. We serve a diverse client base, including public safety, aviation, process control, utilities, and technology, as well as numerous government agencies. With the industry’s largest portfolio of projects worldwide, serving 15 industries, it’s our proven methodology, strict quality standards, and experience that make the difference for our customers. Looking for current openings? Jump on over to our careers page.Our executive team is the most experienced in the industry and provides the thought leadership that positions Evans as the Global Leader in mission-critical operations, console design and manufacturing.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?79946c2d-af38-11ed-be3e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 13:56:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : coreautomation.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>500 mb private info</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79946d08-af38-11ed-bd37-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 13:44:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Mecaro Co., Ltd</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Company Introduction : Mecaro Co., Ltd is No1 Best Semicon parts company authorized in parts area by producing optimal semiconductor part of equipments through ceaseless technology development and research for about 15 years.  ​MORE INFO: https://www.wsj.com/market-data/quotes/KR/241770/financials  LEAKED DATA: https://anonfiles.com/bb60w5Ydy6/PLM_zip                    PASSWORD FOR ARCHIVE: kPl%l!ttuJ8;1Dxali3u1TzO%gk=7tJh </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?79946de3-af38-11ed-8798-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 02:53:46 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Hydrofit Alliance Ltd</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>Hydrofit FZE an ISO 9001, ISO 14001 &amp; 45001 company, pioneering in the field of Fluid Power Transmissions, Mechanical Power Transmissions, Automatic Greasing / Lubrication systems and Oil Recirculation systems  MORE INFO: https://www.zoominfo.com/c/hydrofit-alliance-ltd/346285910?__cf_chl_tk=5mBW2PYNvvqwAbHrTvIe_QmsK7qT8ybeY2RH3Kvmf8w-1676508140-0-gaNycGzND7s  LEAKED DATA: https://anonfiles.com/Y7Q9weYcy2/hydrofitgroup_zip PASSWORD: p&gt;7JEwOJ8i994RC=*69?J&lt;q648H.:xE/ </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?79946ebd-af38-11ed-b49c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 02:53:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : Gallier Orléans</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description>DATA: https://anonfiles.com/NfWdw2Yby8/GALLIER_zipPASSWORD: ?ie(yD@83,%0HR^t6_#S|VW*L6^cA-B\ </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?79946f97-af38-11ed-9c29-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Feb 2023 02:53:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : blackandwhitecabs.com.au</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Dear management! change the negotiator, the conditions he offers are very funny!Cheap, fast and reliable Taxi and Cab services in Brisbane, Perth, Toowoomba, Redcliffe, Maryborough and Mandurah.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79947089-af38-11ed-8061-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 23:37:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : trudi.it</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Trudi si accorge di essere un marchio forte, con un’importante riconoscibilità, capace di trasmettere valori ed emozioni. Trudi non è più solo sinonimo di peluche, ma è in grado di lanciare sul mercato proprie licenze, con importanti partner che ne c...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?7994716a-af38-11ed-90c8-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 23:23:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Foamtec International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>The best of East and West - that is the strength of Foamtec International. Combining Western cutting edge technology with Eastern traditions of dedicated customer service, Foamex Asia was established in 1997 as a joint venture between Foamex International Inc.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?79947243-af38-11ed-93d9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 21:23:33 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : semsinc.net</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>SEMS is a regional environmental management firm with a national reach. Our decades of experience have positioned us to help you navigate complex projects in highly regulated industries. Our team has the training, experience, and expertise to deliver...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?7994731a-af38-11ed-a805-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:58:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vipar.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>VIPAR Heavy Duty is North America’s leading network of independent aftermarket truck parts distributors. VIPAR Heavy Duty distributors serve the needs of their customers from over 560 locations across the United States, Canada, Puerto Rico, and Mexic...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?799473f3-af38-11ed-80dd-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 13:46:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : richardsind.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Richards Industrials is an industrial valve manufacturer located in Cincinnati, Ohio</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?799474ce-af38-11ed-9c35-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:39:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : montibello.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>cosmetics and creams from spain</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?799475bc-af38-11ed-b6b7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:37:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nationallocums.co.uk</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>We’re a locum agency run on family values, helping doctors, nurses and AHPs find the best opportunities in the NHS and independent hospitals. We’re passionate about placing high calibre healthcare professionals to provide the best quality of care to...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?799476bb-af38-11ed-82ee-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 11:25:53 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : PetroChina Indonesia</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>PetroChina Indonesia is a company that operates in the Oil &amp; Energy industry. It employs 251-500 people and has $25M-$50M of revenue. The company is headquartered in Jakarta, Jakarta, Indonesia</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?79947796-af38-11ed-b7e0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 05:26:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : gruppobeltrame.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Active in the iron and steel sector since 1896, AFV Gruppo Beltrame is synonymous with excellence and innovation in the production of merchant bars and special profiles for multiple applications: construction, shipyards and excavators.We have a lot...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?7994786d-af38-11ed-a5ee-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 02:53:27 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Microgame SpA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Italy</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?79947943-af38-11ed-a294-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 23:21:49 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Energie Pool Schweiz</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Zurich, Switzerland</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?79947a35-af38-11ed-83fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 23:20:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Alexandercity</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Your travel and local community guide to Alex City, Alabama. Explore the Alexander City AL directory for hotels, restaurants, shopping, real estate, churches, government, schools, attractions and recreation.City department data.Data of contractors and subcontractors</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?79947b11-af38-11ed-a8a3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Delallo</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Founded in 1950, Delallo is a Company that offers Italian food products such as pasta and grains, sauces, tomatoes, olives, oils, vinegar, cured meats, and pickled vegetables.Headquarters: 1 Delallo Way, Mount Pleasant, Pennsylvania, 15666, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?79947be9-af38-11ed-b8b7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cefcostores.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>WE ARE COMMITTED TO PROVIDING THE BEST CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE.At CEFCO Convenience Stores, we are committed to provide the best customer experience to every customer, every day, at every CEFCO Convenience Stores location. Whether you’re making a quick...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79947cc1-af38-11ed-a39a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 13:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : albanesi.com.ar</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Grupo Albanesi is a business group that engages in the production of thermal electricity and the distribution of natural gas.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79947db4-af38-11ed-a717-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : srf.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>SRF Limited is a multi-business chemicals conglomerate engaged in the manufacturing of industrial and specialty intermediates. The company's business portfolio covers fluorochemicals, specialty chemicals, packaging films, technical textiles, coated a...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79947ea4-af38-11ed-a77e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 09:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Hospital Service SpA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>HS was founded in 1980 with the objective to promote and distribute throughout Italy new methods of minimally invasive interventional diagnostic technologies, introducing on the National market a new generation of echo-guided biopsy products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?79947f9a-af38-11ed-976d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Vitas</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Established in 1995, which is considered as one of the most important specialized programs of the Global Communities Foundation (formerly CHF International for Lending and Financial Services)</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?79948074-af38-11ed-b0d1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Banco Sol</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Banco Sol is a private Angolan bank founded 17 years ago. Headquartered in Luanda, Angola's capital, it's recognised as one of Africa's most successful financial institutions with 940,000 clients on its books and a staff of 1,642. With 180 branches throughout the country.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?7994814f-af38-11ed-8f13-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:06:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Eureka Casino Resort</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Eureka Casinos was founded by the Lee family in Las Vegas, NV. It operates a wide-ranging number of businesses, including Eureka Casino Resort in Mesquite, NV. The Lee Family sold it to the employees in 2015 making it Nevada's first 100% employee owned casino</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?79948227-af38-11ed-9980-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cassaragionieri.it</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Associazione Cassa Nazionale di Previdenza ed Assistenza a favore dei Ragionieri e Periti CommercialiThanks to our work with this company. In our hands is a huge amount of private data. Mail correspondence is not subject to disclosure. Contract...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?79948317-af38-11ed-8d04-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 17:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Reventics</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?79948409-af38-11ed-98c5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Grace Church International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>We Believe the Bible is God's supreme authority of the church and that prayer builds a relationship with God. We believe that faith empowers one to believe the impossible. That family is the foundation of the church and each person has a uniquely designed purpose</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?799484e7-af38-11ed-83f6-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Integerity Tax</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Small business accounting, tax preparation, bookkeeping, payroll, individual taxes</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?799485c4-af38-11ed-b3a4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>