<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Alexandercity</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Your travel and local community guide to Alex City, Alabama. Explore the Alexander City AL directory for hotels, restaurants, shopping, real estate, churches, government, schools, attractions and recreation.City department data.Data of contractors and subcontractors</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?83b67008-ac9e-11ed-8865-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:33:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Delallo</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Founded in 1950, Delallo is a Company that offers Italian food products such as pasta and grains, sauces, tomatoes, olives, oils, vinegar, cured meats, and pickled vegetables.Headquarters: 1 Delallo Way, Mount Pleasant, Pennsylvania, 15666, United States</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?83b687fa-ac9e-11ed-b136-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:32:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cefcostores.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>WE ARE COMMITTED TO PROVIDING THE BEST CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE.At CEFCO Convenience Stores, we are committed to provide the best customer experience to every customer, every day, at every CEFCO Convenience Stores location. Whether you’re making a quick...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b689a2-ac9e-11ed-8204-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 13:41:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : albanesi.com.ar</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Grupo Albanesi is a business group that engages in the production of thermal electricity and the distribution of natural gas.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b68acd-ac9e-11ed-8c96-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 11:23:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : srf.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>SRF Limited is a multi-business chemicals conglomerate engaged in the manufacturing of industrial and specialty intermediates. The company's business portfolio covers fluorochemicals, specialty chemicals, packaging films, technical textiles, coated a...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b68bd5-ac9e-11ed-9fd5-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 09:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : Hospital Service SpA</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>HS was founded in 1980 with the objective to promote and distribute throughout Italy new methods of minimally invasive interventional diagnostic technologies, introducing on the National market a new generation of echo-guided biopsy products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?83b68cc8-ac9e-11ed-a178-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:10:31 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Vitas</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Established in 1995, which is considered as one of the most important specialized programs of the Global Communities Foundation (formerly CHF International for Lending and Financial Services)</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?83b68dc9-ac9e-11ed-8909-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:09:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Banco Sol</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Banco Sol is a private Angolan bank founded 17 years ago. Headquartered in Luanda, Angola's capital, it's recognised as one of Africa's most successful financial institutions with 940,000 clients on its books and a staff of 1,642. With 180 branches throughout the country.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?83b68eb1-ac9e-11ed-96a3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 03:06:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Eureka Casino Resort</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Eureka Casinos was founded by the Lee family in Las Vegas, NV. It operates a wide-ranging number of businesses, including Eureka Casino Resort in Mesquite, NV. The Lee Family sold it to the employees in 2015 making it Nevada's first 100% employee owned casino</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b68f91-ac9e-11ed-b363-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 19:31:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : cassaragionieri.it</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Associazione Cassa Nazionale di Previdenza ed Assistenza a favore dei Ragionieri e Periti CommercialiThanks to our work with this company. In our hands is a huge amount of private data. Mail correspondence is not subject to disclosure. Contract...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6906f-ac9e-11ed-93cb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 17:33:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Reventics</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?83b6914b-ac9e-11ed-840a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 15:17:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Grace Church International</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>We Believe the Bible is God's supreme authority of the church and that prayer builds a relationship with God. We believe that faith empowers one to believe the impossible. That family is the foundation of the church and each person has a uniquely designed purpose</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69226-ac9e-11ed-915b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Integerity Tax</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Small business accounting, tax preparation, bookkeeping, payroll, individual taxes</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69301-ac9e-11ed-8ff4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Aglobis</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Resistance shall not prevent us from fulfilling below mission: We connect industries for their sustainable operation and growth! Above services to be provided on a long term basis, i.e. indefinitely which is represented by the similar symbol in our logo Aglobis</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b693ef-ac9e-11ed-9a53-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : EightPixelsSquare</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Founded in December 2012 and based in Derby, United Kingdom, EightPixelsSquare comprises of an elite team of 45 veteran game developers. Over 30 million players worldwide enjoy EightPixelsSquare's catalogue of games across iOS and Android platforms</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b694e6-ac9e-11ed-851a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Bank of Africa</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Headquartered in the city of Dakar, Senegal, the story of Bank of Africa Group began in Mali in 1982, with the first Bank of Africa, which was created with almost no external help. Since 2010, the Bank of Africa Group has been majority-owned by BMCE Bank.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b695c3-ac9e-11ed-9691-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : European Window</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>European Window Company is an Australian leader in the design and installation of high efficiency thermal break windows, doors and sliding systems.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b6969c-ac9e-11ed-923e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Elektro Richter</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Elektro Richter is a company that operates in the Electrical/Electronic Manufacturing industry. It employs 21-50 people and has $5M-$10M of revenue. The company is headquartered in Hildburghausen, Thuringia, Germany</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69775-ac9e-11ed-8845-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Elim Clinic</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Elim Clinic is a professional treatment centre that offers inpatient treatment to men and women, 18 years and older who suffer from substance use disorders and behaviour addiction. Elim has been in existence for more than six decades and has a wealth of experience</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69853-ac9e-11ed-a770-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : PFA Systems</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>PFA SYSTEMS, Inc. was started over thirty years ago with a single vision in mind, to provide reliable and safety conscientious service to our Suppliers and Drivers.This vision continues to carry on from day one when we were a single operator company, to our current fleet. We currently serve 14 states regionally and continuously work to establish trust between our clients and drivers.We specialize in Hazardous Bulk Liquid transport, but we are not limited to a single product. We integrate cutting edge safety practice and equipment to deliver the peace of mind our customers have come to rely upon and expect.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69948-ac9e-11ed-8ebf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : EnCom</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Founded in 2001, EnCom Inc is a specialty producer of custom compounded high-performance polymers serving the automotive, transportation, electronic, consumer goods, lawn and garden equipment, medical, material handling, and industrial industries.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69a3d-ac9e-11ed-b48a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Diethelm Keller Aviation Pte Ltd </title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Diethelm Keller Aviation Pte Ltd (DKA), a global leader in galley inserts for the airline industry, is a wholly owned subsidiary of Diethelm Keller Brands Ltd. We are headquartered in Singapore.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69b3c-ac9e-11ed-8d38-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 15:05:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ medusa has just published a now post : Tonga Communications</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa</link><description>Tonga Communications Corporation is a government-owned telecommunications provider offering mobile, fixed line, and internet services. It is based in Nuku'alofa. Tonga Communications Corporation Is Tonga's NO.1 cellular, fixedline &amp; internet provider.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/medusa?83b69c1e-ac9e-11ed-8c16-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 15:05:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : dana-group.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>We’re a multi-disciplinary behavioral health organization committed to helping our patients grow personally, socially, and professionally. We’ve been helping people from all walks of life for over 30 years.Our committed team of providers includes...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b69cfc-ac9e-11ed-b21b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 13:53:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : mangalagroup.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Mangala Group, is India’s one of the leading enterprises with businesses in the seafood industry. Mangala group was established by Mr. MV Ramachandra Bhat in 1967. Today, the group has grown to be one of most well-known names in the industry producin...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b69e38-ac9e-11ed-8da0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 13:50:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : nonson.com.vn</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Non Son Fashion is the number one leading fashion for Vietnamese. Non Son is always dedicated to his work and also tries his best to offer customers the best products.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b69f17-ac9e-11ed-aeb2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 13:37:06 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : vanderkaay.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>We’re Passionate About Connecting Investors and Business OwnersVander Kaay is a middle-market M&amp;A intermediary specializing in buy-side deal origination for premier private equity, strategic and family office investors. We source, qualify and intro...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a002-ac9e-11ed-83aa-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:31:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : hidalgocounty.us</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Hidalgo County Community Supervision and Corrections Department is a public agency dedicated to the protection of the community and committed to the belief that facilitating positive change in probationers results in responsible and productive be...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a0e1-ac9e-11ed-a82e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:31:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : tucsoneyecare.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Tucson Eye Care is committed to integrating the latest technology into our practice to provide compassionate, state-of-the-art eye care to our patients.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a1cd-ac9e-11ed-adff-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:31:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : chempartner.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>281 GBContents of downloaded information: company analytics, project information, reports, information on drug supplies, etc.AboutUs: Over the past twenty years, ChemPartner has evolved from the pure chemistry service provider to a research inn...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a2ab-ac9e-11ed-a872-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 11:19:25 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : mdstrucking.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>MDS Logistics is a full-service, third-party Logistics Provider specializing in all phases of transportation management for our customers. MDS Logistics' primary focus is to reduce the customer's total transportation expense, resulting in improvement...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a383-ac9e-11ed-b692-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 09:48:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : laganscg.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Lagan Specialist Contracting | Civil Engineering, Construction, Aviation Infrastructure, Piling, Plant Hire, M&amp;E, Fit… Lagan Airport Mainenance Ltd Home About Specialist Services Responsibilities News Careers Contact Our Companies Our Mission To be a...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a477-ac9e-11ed-ae08-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 09:33:16 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : greekpeak.net</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>WELCOME TO GREEK PEAK Greek Peak Mountain Resort, central New York's largest ski resort was founded in 1958 and has remained at the leading edge of the ski industry with fifty-six trails, six chair lifts, two surface lifts, beginners' slope, and terr...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a554-ac9e-11ed-b537-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2023 07:26:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : lhermite-agri.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>lhermite-agri.comLhermite Agri | Vente de matériel agricole neuf et d'occasion en Ile-de-France, Normandie, région Centre et Pays de la Loire.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a62e-ac9e-11ed-b24b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 23:15:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : olsenlawgroup.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>At Olsen Law Group, we believe that life’s too short to be weighed down by legal issues. We’re here to help.They don't keep your documents safe at all</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a709-ac9e-11ed-a671-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 23:11:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : wilsonart.co.th</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Wilsonart is a global manufacturer and distributor of High Pressure Laminates and other engineered composite materials, used in furniture, office and retail space, countertops, worktops and other applications. Headquartered in Temple, Texas, Wilsonar...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a7f5-ac9e-11ed-a6b2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 23:06:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : ppinvestors.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Founded in 2002, Phoenix Property Investors (“Phoenix”) is an experienced, independently-owned and managed private equity real estate investment group, with a fully integrated investment, project management and asset management platform in Asia.INV...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a8d1-ac9e-11ed-a503-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 23:00:38 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : mhstech.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>fire protection systems</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6a9a9-ac9e-11ed-8e58-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 22:49:02 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vendetta has just published a now post : albouyassociesconsult</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta</link><description>Nos originesCréée en 1946, l'entreprise a durant les trois premières décennies, développé sa notoriété dans le secteur de la coopération agricole sur le plan...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vendetta?83b6aa82-ac9e-11ed-9aa9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 21:27:37 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Inland Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>The Inland Group of Companies is a multi-national collective of premier aviation services providers. Each company is highly specialized in their field of expertise with proven track records of providing safe, efficient, and cost-effective aviation services.Integrated Deicing Services (IDS)Aircraft Deicing and Anti-icing Services.Inland Technologies International/Canada (Inland)Aviation Environmental Services.Quantem Aviation Services (QAS)Ground Handling and Terminal Services.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?83b6ab5a-ac9e-11ed-8d08-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 19:20:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Cork Institute of Technology &amp; Munster Technological University</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Selective data from Cork Institute of Technology &amp; Munster Technological University includes but not limited to :  1)PII Data 2)Confidential Data 3)Financial Data 4)Students personal &amp; medical data (scholarship details) 5)Staff data 6)Students notes &amp; assessments  And more...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?83b6ac38-ac9e-11ed-8180-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 17:20:03 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : mrkpc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Mullin, P.C. is a Dallas-based full-service commercial law firm representing clients in Texas, the U.S., and internationally. Our firm brings together an exceptionally talented group of attorneys with focused experience and knowledge in franchising,...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6ad10-ac9e-11ed-9e11-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 16:39:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : covermeinsurance.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Michael J Poller founded Cover Me Insurance Agency in 1999 and primarily operates in the commercial auto Insurance industry within the Insurance Agents, Brokers and Service sector. Michael has over 45 year experience in the commercial insurance indus...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6ae01-ac9e-11ed-9283-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 16:29:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : I*****</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Medical Testing &amp; Clinical Laboratories.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?83b6aef1-ac9e-11ed-a36b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 13:18:10 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : The Gucciardo Law Firm</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>We are relentlessly committed to our clients as if they were members of our own family. You can turn to us for guidance and honest answers.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?83b6afcc-ac9e-11ed-9546-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 13:17:39 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ bianlian has just published a now post : Danielski Farms Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian</link><description>Danielski Farms Inc. strives to perform the highest quality and efficient harvest of our customers’ crops. Being farmers ourselves, we know the painstaking efforts required to see a crop through from planting to harvest.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/bianlian?83b6b0a6-ac9e-11ed-bc8c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 13:17:08 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : maysecc.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Mayse Construction is a Construction company located in 8011 Hixson Pike, Hixson, Tennessee, United States. Since 1985 the company has been providing Sewer Line Construction.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6b17e-ac9e-11ed-ac91-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 11:56:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : interpaving.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Interpaving Limited is a privately held company formed in 1972. The company's head office is located in Sudbury, Ontario, with a regional office in Timmins, Ontario. The company specializes in site servicing, paving, concrete sidewalk and curbs, exca...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?83b6b256-ac9e-11ed-a5a0-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:16:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 0mega has just published a now post : Aviacode (GeBBS)</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/0mega</link><description>Medical coding, outsourced coding, auditing &amp; consulting</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/0mega?83b6b32f-ac9e-11ed-9bcf-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 02:46:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ daixin has just published a now post : B&amp;G Foods (CA, US)</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/daixin</link><description>B&amp;G Foods, Inc. manufactures, sells, and distributes a portfolio of shelf-stable and frozen foods, and household products in the United States, Canada, and Puerto Rico.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/daixin?83b6b407-ac9e-11ed-9806-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 23:14:04 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>