<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link><description>Last 50 entries monitoring by Ransomware.live</description><image><url>https://www.ransomware.live/ransomwarelive.png</url><title>Ransomware.live RSS Feed</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/rss.xml</link></image><item><title>🏴‍☠️ ransomhouse has just published a now post : IMI Hydronic Engineering</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse</link><description>IMI plc is a global engineering group that focuses on precision fluid engineering. IMI plc incorporates three divisions, each working to make its vision come to life – IMI Hydronic, Norgren and IMI Critical.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/ransomhouse?72e7a1f4-924c-11ed-b5af-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 08:38:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ snatch has just published a now post : Physician Partners of America</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch</link><description>Founded in 2013 by a physician-turned-entrepreneur, Physician Partners of America aims to offer patients a safe, seamless healthcare experience and doctors who can totally focus on patients. Physician Partners of America offers pain management, orthopedics, minimally invasive laser spine surgery, mental health counseling. We are</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/snatch?72e7be3c-924c-11ed-bc6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 05:22:47 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ hive has just published a now post : G.W. Becker</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive</link><description>***** DATA IS COMING SOON ****  G.W. Becker, Inc. is a full service, single source, provider of choice for quality overhead crane products and solutions. Family owned since 1980, we have grown from a local overhead crane parts supplier to a recognized industry leader offering a full spectrum of overhead crane related products and services throughout North America.  Proud to be an Executive Member of the Crane Manufacturer’s Association of America, we design and manufacture custom overhead cranes, hoists and components to CMAA Specifications (Class “A” through “F”) or AIST Technical Report #6. We utilize our knowledgeable in-house team of mechanical, structural and electrical engineers to offer application assistance, custom design engineering and manufacturing of overhead crane products with our customers’ needs first and foremost.  Empowered with highly trained and qualified technicians, G.W. Becker, Inc. provides self-performing installations, inspections and field service repairs for all makes and models of overhead cranes; providing compliance with local regulations and ensuring a safe and productive material handling operation.  Staying true to our mission and values, we strive to understand our customers’ needs and deliver specialized expertise and long-term planning solutions for the unique challenges of purchasing and maintaining overhead crane and hoist equipment. </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive?72e7c01c-924c-11ed-a8a4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:19:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : D???? P??????s</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?72e7c17a-924c-11ed-8d5f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 20:39:01 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : A????? ????k</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>United Kingdom</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?72e7c2b0-924c-11ed-828d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 19:41:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Liebra Permana</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Liebra Permana PT was founded in 1999. The company's line of business includes the manufacturing of womens and childrens underwear.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?72e7c3d2-924c-11ed-8cb3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:36:11 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : TIME TECHNOPLAST LIMITED</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Time Technoplast engages in manufacturing and suppling of polymer packaging products. Time Technoplast was founded in 1992.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?72e7c508-924c-11ed-aba3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 17:34:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : circlevillecourt.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Welcome to The Circleville Municipal Court website. The court serves all of Pickaway County with countywide jurisdiction.We downloaded more than 500 gigabytes of different dates. Customer data. Nanny criminals. Case information. And much more. In...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?72e7c616-924c-11ed-bac3-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 11:23:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ mallox has just published a now post : ADIVA CO. LTD</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/mallox?72e7c724-924c-11ed-9a6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 09:22:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : datair.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Your negotiator obviously already got the operating money to solve this situation, but since now there is a slight upward trend in BTC - apparently he wants to make a little more money on this growth. No need to play with us. You have a deadline of J...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?72e7c832-924c-11ed-8eba-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 17:33:58 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Chestertons Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?72e7c936-924c-11ed-b15b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 15:22:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Fire Rescue Victoria</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Fire Rescue Victoria is a fire and rescue service in the state of Victoria, Australia, that provides firefighting, rescue, HAZMAT and Emergency Medical Response services in areas of metropolitan Melbourne and major regional centres throughout Victoria.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7cad0-924c-11ed-985d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:42:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Thor Specialties, Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?72e7cc06-924c-11ed-8779-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:42:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lorenz has just published a now post : Shelco</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lorenz?72e7cd5a-924c-11ed-b571-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2023 13:41:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ 0mega has just published a now post : Aviacode</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/0mega</link><description>Medical coding, outsourced coding, auditing &amp; consulting</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/0mega?72e7ce68-924c-11ed-aff1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 19:24:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ karakurt has just published a now post : River City Science Academy</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/karakurt</link><description>River City Science Academy (RCSA) is a tuition-free, public charter school located in Duval County in Jacksonville, Florida. RCSA was founded in 2007 and currently serves grades K – 12 through 4 different locations. RCSA offers an emphasis on STEM education. In this release we will show you 63 GB of RCSA's data which include financials, executive and accounting information as well as a great amount of personal student and employee data.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/karakurt?72e7cfbc-924c-11ed-9d4e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 15:18:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : asianrecorp.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>The Asian Reinsurance Corporation is an intergovernmental organization established in May 1979 under the auspices of the UN-ESCAP. Membership is open to all state members or associate members of the United Nations Economic and Social Commission for A...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?72e7d0de-924c-11ed-b165-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 19:03:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Koo Wee Rup Secondary College</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Koo Wee Rup Secondary College prides itself on building guided pathways with a wholistic approach around student centred learning. KWRSC is a Year 7 to 12 inclusive college with just over 1100 students on one campus.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?72e7d1ec-924c-11ed-a9be-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 18:04:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : millennia.pro</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>ENGINEERING  CONSULTING SERVICES 22.44 GB DATA</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?72e7d2f0-924c-11ed-961b-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 11:22:44 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Fruttagel</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Fruttagel was founded in 1994 when the Alfonsine plant in Ravenna was established. It combines the legacies of two important players working together in the field: Ala Frutta, a cooperative founded in the early 1960s, specializing in the processing of fresh fruit</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?72e7d3f4-924c-11ed-a72e-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 21:45:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ avoslocker has just published a now post : Corporate Interiors Inc</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/avoslocker</link><description>Corporate Interiors - Steelcase office furniture - Delaware and Philadelphia Contact Us 1-800-690-9101</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/avoslocker?72e7d516-924c-11ed-a5e4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:30:32 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Duty Free Philippines</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Duty Free Philippines - In the service of Philippine Tourism. As a government corporation, DFPC is tasked to operate the duty-and tax-free merchandising system in the Philippines to augment the service facilities for tourists and to generate foreign exchange and revenue for the government.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7d688-924c-11ed-85fc-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:25:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Swift Academies</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>The aim of the Swift Academies is to build, strengthen and expand our Trust across the North of England, by incorporating good and outstanding schools into our family of academies and acting as a sponsor for other primary and secondary academies, aiming to help them improve their standards and performance.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7d7a0-924c-11ed-925f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:21:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : 100x100banco.com</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>100%BancoCaracas, Venezuela</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?72e7d8a4-924c-11ed-8a7d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 12:09:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : juarez.gob.mx</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Gobierno MunicipalH. Ayuntamiento de JuárezUnidad Administrativa Benito JuárezAv. Francisco Villa 950 N., CentroC.P. 32000, Juárez, Chihuahua656 737 0000</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?72e7d9a8-924c-11ed-b9de-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:56:52 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Buffco Production, Inc.</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Buffco Production, Inc. is a native East Texas exploration and production company with more than 35 years of experience in the oil and natural gas industry. Buffco strives to drill and produce oil and gas efficiently and keep its owners informed while maintaining industry standards. Buffco understands the continuously evolving practices and technologies in the oil and gas industry, and has significant expertise with combatting shifting commodities markets. Buffco can navigate current producing properties, while methodically evaluating new prospects and strategically choosing those that fit current climates. Buffco’s adaptability and expansive knowledge base of conventional and unconventional oil and gas development are the reasons why it has had scalable growth over decades past.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?72e7daac-924c-11ed-8d56-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Grupo Estrategas EMM</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description>Grupo Estrategas S.A. de C.V es una empresa 100 % mexicana comprometida con el mercado asegurador mexicano y socialmente responsable con todos nuestros clientes, proveedores y empleados.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?72e7dbb0-924c-11ed-9930-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ alphv has just published a now post : Pendulum Associates public website of data leak</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/alphv?72e7dd0e-924c-11ed-9d8c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 11:26:42 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ lockbit3 has just published a now post : takamiya.co</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3</link><description>Takamiya provides total services from development/manufacturing, sales, rental, design/construction, management/distribution of various products including temporary equipment .Takamiya Co., LtdWe create products and services with high added value...</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/lockbit3?72e7de1c-924c-11ed-a199-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2023 09:14:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Park View</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Park View is a high performing community school in Tottenham, north London where your child will aspire, achieve and succeed.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7df20-924c-11ed-b515-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Bay Area Rapid Transit</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>The San Francisco Bay Area Rapid Transit District is a heavy-rail public transit system that connects the San Francisco Peninsula with communities in the East Bay and South Bay. BART operates in five counties with 131 miles of track and 50 stations, carrying approximately 405,000 trips on an average weekday.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7e01a-924c-11ed-a3f2-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:20:23 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : City Lit</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Whether you are looking to kick-start a new career, delve into a favourite topic, keep active or bring some balance to a busy life, City Lit offer a huge range of courses.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7e16e-924c-11ed-80e1-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 21:18:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : LEK / HABO</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Lek/Habo realiseert al tientallen jaren met succes innovatieve en toonaangevende energie- en installatietechnische projecten in binnen- en buitenland.Onze vestigingen in Ter Aar (voorheen Lek Installatietechniek) en in Bodegraven (voorheen Habo) hebben hun krachten gebundeld om nog beter complexe turnkey projecten te ontwerpen, produceren, installeren en onderhouden.Met Lek/Habo bouwen we samen aan een duurzame toekomst.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?72e7e290-924c-11ed-b885-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 17:25:55 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : Bevolution Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Food &amp; Beverage · Illinois, United States﻿Bevolution Group produces shelf-stable and frozen beverage products, and cocktail mixes.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?72e7e39e-924c-11ed-93c7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 11:18:48 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : PROQUINAL Spradling Group</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>A team of over 1,800 people who work every day with the desire to inspire the world with designs that move people, innovations that are lasting, and products that make spaces more attractive. Always with the commitment of caring for the environment and communities we're a part of. We are Spradling: Inspiration that covers the world.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7e4f2-924c-11ed-a1b4-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : Sub-drill Supply</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>Sub-drill was incorporated in 1992 and is a proven and trusted manufacturer and supplier of Subsea Tools and Drilling Equipment to the Global Energy Industry.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7e61e-924c-11ed-91cb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:19:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ vicesociety has just published a now post : LetMeRepair</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety</link><description>We are company focusing on supporting the complete, "presales" and "after sales cycles" for the IT, office automation, consumer Electronics and telecommunication, robotics and electromobility industries. LetMeRepair has set its goal to be the most efficient service company while achieving the highest possible customer satisfaction.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/vicesociety?72e7e722-924c-11ed-8abe-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 09:17:30 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ hive has just published a now post : Consulate Health Care</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive</link><description>Consulate Health Care is a leading provider of senior healthcare services, specializing in post-acute care. We offer services ranging from comprehensive short-term rehabilitation and transitional care to Alzheimer’s and dementia care. Consulate Health Care began as a small provider in Cheswick, PA with a strong focus on patient needs. We haven’t waivered from that focus, which has strengthened our family and allows us to sustain jobs in many communities, create rigorous systems of care and deploy technology that makes it easier to understand patient needs. Even as we’ve grown to provide services across 5 states, it’s the little things we do while fulfilling our mission statement of "Providing Service with Our Hearts and Hands" that really makes the difference. From visiting with our patients while they eat, to pulling up the sheets to just the right height, our employees care for patients like family, not because it’s their job, but because it’s their calling.  </description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/hive?72e7e826-924c-11ed-88fb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2023 07:20:24 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Ellison Technologies</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>Ellison Technologies is a provider of advanced machining solutions to North American metal-cutting manufacturers and their global affiliates. As a family of companies we are committed to the survival and growth of the American manufacturing industry.  Independent offices provide us a local market focus and the flexibility to advocate the needs of each of our valued customers. Our priority is to introduce technologies that strengthen our customers’ ability to compete in the markets they serve.  Whether the solution involves a stand alone machine, multi-process equipment, or an integrated manufacturing system with robotic automation, our goal remains the same; to optimize throughput and quality at the lowest per-part manufacturing cost.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?72e7e970-924c-11ed-82ba-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:39:21 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Hayward</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>Come on in... The water is Hayward. At Hayward®, we're more than just equipment. Our objective is to make your pool experience worry and hassle-free. That's why our equipment is engineered to last and work smart at keeping your pool sparkling clean and trouble free. For over 80-years, we've been helping pool owners enjoy the pleasures of pool ownership by manufacturing cutting edge, technologically advanced pool equipment worldwide. We strive to ensure that your Totally Hayward™ System operates at maximum efficiency all season long. Our goal is that at the end of the day, your only concern is to turn your equipment on and off. Whether you are trying to create the perfect backyard environment, reduce operating and maintenance costs through the ease of wireless controls, Hayward is your single source solution. Our products include a complete line of technologically advanced pumps, filters, heaters, heat pumps, automatic pool cleaners, lighting, controls and salt chlorine generators—high-quality components engineered to work together to keep your pool at its best. Hayward aims to take the worry out of pool ownership by developing products that are efficient, require little maintenance and add value to your investment.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?72e7ea74-924c-11ed-9b7f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:37:20 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : Kansas City Homes</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>From our earliest days in Kansas City, we have remained brokerage leaders in the real estate industry by developing relationships with our clients and our communities. The Better Homes and Gardens® Real Estate brand was built upon a passion for the home. Sellers benefit from this well-known brand through the exposure generated by millions of home searches online and the inherent trust of the iconic brand.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?72e7eb78-924c-11ed-b3e7-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 17:35:18 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ royal has just published a now post : DSBJ DATA LEAK</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal</link><description>Suzhou Dongshan Precision Manufacturing Co., Ltd. produces and sells critical components for IoT intelligence, telecommunication equipment, metal precision,8 Fenghuangshan Rd, Suzhou, Jiangsu, 215107, China+86 51266281215Suzhou Dongshan Precision Manufacturing Co LtdFrom specialized production to outstanding accomplishments, we are always advancing forwards. From a small factory to an international enterprise, our roots spread wider with each passing day. From insightful vision to leading the future, we continue to build on our legacy.DSBJ is a leading worldwide technology partner providing critical components for IoT intelligence, with a special focus on Telecommunication Equipment and Metal Precision, LED technologies and Interconnect solutions. With a vision focused on technological breakthroughs, we constantly bring new innovative solutions, high-tech products and high-quality services that propel our customers to success.DSBJ takes surefooted steps forward and takes them quickly. In April 2010, 30 years after our inception, we were listed on the Shenzhen Stock Exchange. We?ve continually evolved over three decades, perpetually innovating and strategically transforming ourselves time and time again. From a small manufacturing company to a prestigious global player, our successful journey is testament to our vision, innovative spirit and determined belief in technology. As we embrace future challenges, we will remain steadfast in our pursuit to benefit both stakeholders and the wider society.Technological innovation is in our DNA and is the cornerstone of DSBJ. With cutting-edge production facilities and advanced technology, we constantly deliver state-of-the-art products and quality services. Our global network of research bases and offices keeps us abreast of the latest tech breakthroughs, so we can effectively allocate resources wherever they're needed. With an established presence in mainland China, Taiwan, South Korea, Finland, India, Sweden, Germany, Poland, Estonia, the US and Mexico, we meet customer needs quickly and competently, providing sales locally in addition to customer service and warehousing capabilities.While deeply proud of our past, we never lose focus of the future. We believe that each and every step is a starting point. Through investments, acquisitions and new facilities, we?ve streamlined our business and expanded frontiers. In 2016 we boosted our revenue by acquiring NASDAQ-listed MFLEX, a top 5 player globally in the FPC industry, operating from the US. In July 2018 we acquired another world-renowned company from the US: PCB solution specialists Multek.At DSBJ, we embrace every opportunity while keeping up to speed with the changing landscape. We consistently explore new avenues and seek next-generation breakthroughs. Looking forward, we have the unwavering determination to deliver critical components and innovative solutions that advance IoT development and build a smarter, more connected world. DSBJ, building a better-connected world for tomorrow.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/royal?72e7ec7c-924c-11ed-979f-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 05:18:19 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : CGMLLC.NET</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?72e7eda8-924c-11ed-b338-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2023 02:35:28 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ clop has just published a now post : UNISALLE.EDU.CO</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/clop?72e7ef60-924c-11ed-9d9c-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 23:09:22 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ blackbyte has just published a now post : CAPMC</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte</link><description>Community Action Partnership of Madera County (CAPMC). Since it was incorporated in 1965, CAPMC has been making a positive difference in our county. CAPMC is committed to improving the social well-being and economic capacity of low to moderate-income individuals and families, as well as providing opportunities to achieve economic independence.</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/blackbyte?72e7f0a0-924c-11ed-b9e9-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2023 17:27:51 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Tarntank Ship Management</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?72e7f1ae-924c-11ed-925a-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 23:15:59 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ everest has just published a now post : Aeronautics company Canada | UTC Aerospace Systems, Bombardier, NASA partners</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/everest</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/everest?72e7f2bc-924c-11ed-ac91-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 19:22:36 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Sirius Shipping</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?72e7f3ca-924c-11ed-bc6d-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:26:50 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : SUNY Polytechnic Institute</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description /><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?72e7f4ce-924c-11ed-afeb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 17:25:40 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>🏴‍☠️ play has just published a now post : Furetank</title><link>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play</link><description>Donso, Vaestra Goetaland, Sweden</description><guid>https://www.ransomware.live/#/profiles/play?72e7f5e6-924c-11ed-93cb-0000499602d2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2023 13:40:58 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>